<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Search><pages Count="106"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Organised By



















                             22 – 24 September, 2022

                             Dar-Es-Salaam, Tanzania






                                Exhibitor Directory]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[CONTENTS


          Messages                                                    5

          About EEPC India                                           21

          List of  Exhibitors                                        23
          Road Map from Hotel To Exhibition Center                   89
          Swahili - English commonly used expressions                90

          Important Contact Numbers – Indian Missions, Hospitals,    96
          Fire Stations,Banks, Shops
          Key  Tourist attractions in  Tanzania                      98

          EEPC India Office Address                                100]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Chairman’s Pen
                 EEPC  India has successfully organized 41  editions  of one of the
              largest Indian engineering exhibitions overseas, now scheduled to be
              held in Tanzania over 22-24 September, 2022.
                 India is among the top five suppliers to Tanzania with significant
              share in  their  import basket. Hence  India  already has  a considerable
              presence in Tanzania’s engineering import basket The INDEE organised
              by EEPC India in Tanzania is one such step towards a deeper and more
              beneficial cooperation between the two countries

                 India’s engineering exports to Tanzania  for 2021-22  recorded at
              USD 550.1 million, registered  a growth of more than 70% over 2020-
              21.
                 The  Indian  market  has  huge potential  in  terms  of  indigenously
              manufactured  products and exporting them to other countries. I would
              like to thank High Commission of India in Tanzania, High Commission
              of the United  Republic  of Tanzania  in  India, Tanzania  Chamber of
              Commerce, Industry & Agriculture and Expo Group

                 I wish good luck to all the participants for INDEE Tanzania 2022




              (Mahesh Desai)
              Chairman, EEPC India]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[From the desk of  Past Chairman &
                    Chairman of Publicity, Exhibition and Delegation
                                Committee, EEPC India

                 India- the fastest growing G-20 economy in FY22 with 9% GDP
              growth, Second highest  producer  of crude steel and consumer of
              finished steel, Third highest most attractive investment destination for
              technology transactions & Resident patent applications; Eighth highest
              in Scientific Publications and Scientific & Technical Manpower  is the
              nation World is looking at proudly and with anticipation.

                 Quoting Hon’ble Prime  Minister  of India, we  say the  world  has
              started searching for solutions to the problems on the soil of India. This
              change in the world, this change in the thinking of the world, is the
              result of our success which has  made the nation among the leading
              leagues in the world.
                 FY  22  Trade  performance  manifested  two historic  highs,  USD
              419.7 billion  total Merchandise exports and USD 112.1 billion  total
              Engineering Exports. The best performing engineering products include
              iron and steel and its products with 69.6 % YoY rise in Exports, 55.7%
              rise in Machine Tools exports , 44.6 % rise in Auto and its Parts, 38.7%
              rise in Pumps exports;  37.9 % rise in Hand and Cutting Tools Exports
              ,27.6%  rise in Electrical Machinery exports and   25.4% rise  in Medical
              and Scientific Instruments .]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[EEPC India  has  been  playing an  active  role in  taking  Indian
             engineering to overseas market and INDEE is one big step towards this
             endeavor.
                The INDEE in Tanzania would definitely provide the big push to
             Exports and I wish the exposition all success.






             (Rakesh Shah)
             Past Chairman & Chairman of Publicity, Exhibition and
             Delegation Committee, EEPC India]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Words from the Chairman of the Committee on
                     Trade with Central, Eastern & Southern Africa
                 India and Tanzania share traditionally close, friendly and cooperative
              bilateral relations. Tanzania emerges as an important partner for India in
              its aim to deepen its economic role in the East African region. Even after
              the COVID 19 pandemic the official GDP of the country has expanded
              in the first half of 2021 and is expected to strengthen over the next two
              years.
                 Tanzania has a substantial share in India’s engineering exports to East
              Africa which rose from 22% during 2020-2021  to 27% in 2021-2022.
              Industrial Machinery, Products of Iron and Steel, Electrical Machinery
              and Equipment, Two and Three Wheelers, Construction Machinery are
              few of the leading Indian Engineering Products exported to Tanzania.

                 EEPC India’s show INDEE-Tanzania 2022 is scheduled from 22-24
              September. This will give an opportunity to our Indian exhibitors to
              expand the market in the East African region. INDUSMACH AFRICA
              2022  and East  Africa  International Trade Exhibition are the other
              concurrent shows which will run parallel with INDEE.
                 I wish  all the best  to the participants  and EEPC India Team for
              INDEE Tanzania. I wish all our participants gain the maximum contacts
              to increase the business  in  the African Market.
              Sd/-

              (Mr Rohinton R. Engineer)
              Chairman of the Committee on  Trade with Central,
              Eastern & Southern Africa,EEPC India]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[ED’s Words



                 India’s largest overseas  engineering exhibition  INDEE after
              completing 45 years, traversing 27 nations is all set for the 42nd edition
              from 22-24  September, 2022  in Tanzania. EEPC India is organising
              in association with Department of Commerce, Government of India;
              Tanzania Chamber of Commerce, Industry and Agriculture (TCCIA)
              and  Indian  High  Commission  in Tanzania. The Tanzania  edition  of
              INDEE will be co-located with three concurrent shows – the 22nd
              INDUSMACH Africa 2022, Tools and Hardware Africa, and East Africa
              International Trade Exhibition 2022.  The shows will provide the Indian
              manufacturers exposure to explore export opportunities in the entire
              Eastern and Central Africa.

                 Tanzania remains one of the key contributors to East Africa’s growing
              prosperity ranked as one of the top ten fastest growing economies in
              2020 globally by NASDAQ.Tanzania has a substantial share in India’s
              engineering exports  to East Africa. In terms of engineering, India’s
              exports to Tanzania stood at USD 550.10 million in 2021-22. The total
              bilateral trade between India and Tanzania stood at USD 4.58 billion  in
              2021-22 recording a 92.93 percent growth from the same period last
              year.]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[This is the first time INDEE is venturing into Tanzania making it
             the 28th nation with an expected team of over 80 Indian exhibitors
             representing  more than 28 Engineering  Product  Panels  including  –
             Electrical Machinery,  Motor Vehicles, Agricultural equipment, Articles
             of Iron & Steel, Packaging Machinery, Hand Tools, Wires and cables to
             name a few.






             (Suranjan Gupta)
             Executive Director, EEPC India]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[Message

                Indusmach  2022 International  Trade Exhibition on Industrial
             Products, Equipment and Machinery is one of the longest running trade
             event held annually in Tanzania creating unmatched opportunities for
             the business community in East Africa. The international event has been
             projected as the ideal forum for export oriented companies to showcase
             their products and services to the huge business community. Tanzania
             itself remains a key and exciting country for investors willing to explore
             the opportunities and make inroads into this lucrative market. Our event
             brings together the leaders of the East African industry by becoming a
             leading source for new products, services and technology from around
             the world.
                The East African  region continues to remain  highly competitive
             in terms of GDP growth, compared to the rest of Africa. Tanzania
             in  particular  has  maintained  a  relatively high  economic  growth  over
             the last decade, averaging around 6-7%  annually. Key strengths and
             opportunities include political stability, an abundance of natural resources,
             strategic geographic location, and immense development potential for
             manufacturing industry. Important economic  drivers like the Export
             Zone  Processing  Authority (EPZA), Confederation  of  Tanzania
             Industries  (CTI),  Tanzania  Bureau of  Standards  (TBS)  &  Tanzania
             Investment Centre (TIC) and numerous other partners have worked
             to accelerate  manufacturing and help the country achieve structural]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[transformation.  The Government of  Tanzania has made it a priority
             to attract foreign direct investment and revive the manufacturing sector
             into one of the fastest growing in the region.
                We are happy to share space and welcome EEPC India’s flagship
             overseas  multi-sectoral  Engineering Exhibition  INDEE in Tanzania
             which will coincide with the 22nd Indusmach Africa 2022 held from
             22nd – 24th September, 2022.

                This is first time INDEE is venturing in Tanzania making it the
             28th nation to host  the event with an expected team of over 80
             Indian exhibitors representing more than 28 Engineering Product
             Panels including -  Electrical Machinery, Motor Vehicles, Agricultural
             Equipment, Articles of Iron & Steel, Packaging Machinery, Hand Tools,
             Wires and Cables to name a few.

                I wish  good luck  to the Indian participants  and thank you for
             making this exposition impactful with INDEE’s presence.

                Sd/-
             (Mr. Duncan Njage )
             Regional Director - East Africa, Expogroup
             Organiser of Indusmach Tanzania 2022]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-110
                 About EEPC India



                 EEPC India  has  been    the  Face  of  Indian  Engineering  Exports
              over a span of 66 years when India grew from a meagre $10 million
              engineering export nation in 1955  to USD 112.1  billion (2021-
              2022)  and is  regarded as the MODEL EPC in India by the Union
              Ministry of Commerce and Industry. EEPC India is the premier trade
              and investment promotion organisation in India. It is sponsored by the
              Ministry of Commerce & Industry, Government of India and caters to
              the Indian engineering sector. It has many firsts to its credit. The First
              Indian EPC to have a website, to be ISO certified, to have a Mobile
              App, to have an in- house Technology Centre and also to e-catalogue
              the product profiles.  As an advisory body it actively contributes in the
              policies of Government of India and acts a prime conduit between the
              Indian Engineering fraternity and the Government. Set up in 1955,
              EEPC India now has a membership base of over 13,000 predominantly
              drawing 60% from MSME segment. EEPC India has been participating
              and  organising  promotional  activities  including  buyer-seller meets
              (BSM) – managing India pavilion in selected overseas exhibitions to
              demonstrate  the  capabilities  of  Indian  engineering  industry.  INDEE
              (Indian Engineering Exhibition and its domestic counterpart – IESS
              (International Engineering Sourcing Show) are two flagship events of
              EEPC India.
                 EEPC India in its endeavour to facilitate the members to continue
              the business  momentum during COVID-19 pandemic, started
              organising e-sessions or webinars and virtual exhibitions, since April
              2020. We have organised over 400 webinars. Over 100 e BSMs have
              been arranged  associating  with around 41 Indian  overseas  Missions
              USA, UAE, Germany, Vietnam, France, Oman, South Korea, Russia,
              Peru, Senegal, Mozambique, Botswana, Thailand, Guatemala, Honduras,]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[El Salvador, Kuwait, South Africa, Uzbekistan, Brazil, Canada, Mexico,
             Qatar, Kenya, Uganda, Nigeria,  Tanzania, Switzerland, Sri  Lanka,
             Ethiopia, EU,  Vietnam, Cameroon, Cambodia, Brunei, Myanmar, Laos,
             Malaysia, Indonesia, Singapore, Philippines.  Virtual Exhibitions on
             Subcontracting, Farm Machinery, Medical Devices, Pumps and Valves,
             Electrical Equipment, Builder Hardware, Metal Cutting, Forming and
             Welding & Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning and Refrigeration
             Equipment have been organised to bolster Engineering exports in these
             sector and more are in the offing.

                Extending its  regular agenda, EEPC India also published  several
             reports/studies  to make the  members  aware about the international
             trends and opportunities in order to enhance their global footprints.








































         22]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[LIST OF EXHIBITORS

              SL.   COMPANY NAME (Alphabetically)                                                       PAGE NO.
              1.   ACME ENGINEERING INDUSTRIES                     27
              2.   AIRA 4MATIC GLOBAL VALVE AUTOMATION PVT LTD     27
              3.   ALFA SWITCHGEAR (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED         28
              4.   AMI ENTERPRISES PVT.LTD.                        28
              5.   ANG EXIM LLP                                    30
              6.   ANSHUMAN TECH PVT. LTD.                         29
              7.   ASSOMAC MACHINES LIMITED                        30
              8.   ATLAS MACHINES (INDIA)                          32
              9.   BEML LIMITED                                    32
              10.  BRAHMANI ENTERPRISE                             34
              11.  DAGA POLYLAMINATORS PVT. LTD.                   35
              12.  DEPROCON CONTROLS                               35
              13.  DGC INDUSTRIES PRIVATE LIMITED                  36
              14.  ECOSURE PULPMOLDING TECHNOLOGIES LTD            37
              15.  ELECTRONIC AUTOMATION PRIVATE LIMITED           37
              16.  FERTIPLANT ENGINEERING CO. PVT. LTD.            38
              17.  FRONTIER TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED           38
              18.  G.K. XIANGHE ELECTRICALS PVT. LTD.              39
              19.  GI AGRO TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LTD                39
              20.  GOVERNMENT OF JHARKHAND                         42
              21.  HARSH PRANJAL INSTRUMENT & POWER PRIVATE LIMITED   42
              22.  HEAT BIRD PVT LTD                               78
              23.  HIMALAYA MACHINERY PVT LTD                      43
              24.  HIRANI AUTOMOTIVE INDUSTRIES                    43
              25.  HOOGHLY ALLOY AND STEELS CO. PVT LTD            44
              26.  HTC VALVES PRIVATE LIMITED                      44
              27.  HYDROPOWER TECH ENGINEERING                     46
              28.  IMPRESS APPAREL MACHINES PVT L                  46

                                                                           23]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[SL.   COMPANY NAME (Alphabetically)                                                       PAGE NO.
           29.  INDIA AGROVISION IMPLEMENTS PV                  48
           30.  INDUSTRIAL BOILERS LTD.                         50
           31.  JEYALETSHMI MACHINE WORKS                       50
           32.  KAY BOUVET ENGINEERING LTD.                     47
           33.  LEGION EXIM LLP                                 47
           34.  LPR EXPORTS ENGINE COMPONENTS PVT LTD           52
           35.  M.L TOOLS INDUSTRIES                            52
           36.  MAG HARD INSULATORS                             53
           37.  MAGCORE LAMINATION (INDIA) PRI                  53
           38.  MAKSON MACHINERY PVT. LTD.                      54
           39.  MARUTHI ELECTRODES PVT.LTD.                     54
           40.  METAL AIDS INDIA                                56
           41.  MK LIDE AUTO CLUTCH INDUSTRIES (P) LTD          56
           42.  MUEZ-HEST INDIA PVT. LTD                        58
           43.  MW WIRETEC PVT. LTD.                            60
           44.  NAVEENA ZEAL TECHNOLOGIES                       58
           45.  NIPHA EXPORTS (P) LTD.                          57
           46.  NIPHA INDIA (P) LIMITED                         57
           47.  NOVA ENGINEERING                                62
           48.  OMKAR ENTERPRISE                                62
           49.  OZLA PLASTOCRAFT PVT. LTD.                      61
           50.  PETRO VALVES PVT LTD                            61
           51.  PIONEER COLD STORE AND CLADDING PVT. LTD.       64
           52.  PLATINUM OVERSEAS                               65
           53.  POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA                 71
           54.  PRIMAX EQUIPMENT PRIVATE LTD.                   64
           55.  PRISM SURFACE COATINGS PRIVATE LIMITED          66
           56.  RAX HYDRAULICS PRIVATE LIMITED                  66
           57.  REMI ELEKTROTECHNIK LTD.                        68
           58.  ROSS BOILERS                                    68

         24]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[SL.   COMPANY NAME (Alphabetically)                                                       PAGE NO.

           59.  ROYAL ARC ELECTRODE LTD                         69
           60.  SENOR METALS PVT. LTD                           70
           61.  SHARP ELECTRODES PVT LTD                        70
           62.  SHIV-OM BRASS INDUSTRIES                        71
           63.  SHREE SAI STEELS                                72
           64.  SHRI VISHVAKARMA (EMERY STONES                  74
           65.  SINGHSONS REFRIGERATION                         74
           66.  SONA CYCLE INDUSTRIES                           73
           67.  SPEEDCRAFTS INFRATECH  PRIVATE                  76
           68.  SRI BHAVANI CASTINGS LTD                        76
           69.  SRP CRANE CONTROLS (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED      77
           70.  STRIKING INTERNATIONAL                          78
           71.  SUMITEK NATRAJ MACHINERY PRIVATE LIMITED        79
           72.  TECHNOCRATS PLASMA SYSTEMS PRIVATE LIMITED      79
           73.  TEJAS POLYMERS AND ENGINEERS                    80
           74.  TFI FILTRATION (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED          81
           75.  TOSY AUTO PRODUCTS                              81
           76.  TRIKON MACHINE PVT. LTD.                        82
           77.  UNIQUE ENGINEERING ENTERPRISES PRIVATE LIMITED   82
           78.  UNIQUE WELDING PRODUCTS PVT LTD                 84
           79.  UNITECHENGINEERING                              84
           80.  USHA LINER SHAPAR PVT LTD                       85
           81.  VENTILATION ENGINEERING CO PVT LTD.             86
           82.  VGK ELECTRIC VEHICLE INDUSTRY PVT LTD           87
           83.  WESMAN THERMAL ENGINEERING PRO                  85
           84.  YAMA ENGINEERS & TESTING INSTRUMENTS PVT LTD    88


        * This order could not be maintained on all the pages inside while mapping the advertisements with the
        company names



                                                                           25]]></page><page Index="28"><![CDATA[26]]></page><page Index="29"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-170
        ACME ENGINEERING INDUSTRIES

        82, Ashokpura,, Near Laxmi Tranks Works,
        Cross Road, Dudheshwar, Ahemdabad-380004,Gujarat,India

        Tel                       :   91-79-25625615
        E-mail                    :   info@acmepumpindia.com
        Website                   :   www.acmepumpindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :  Mr. Manzil S Patel,
        & Participant               Partner
        Range of Products         :   Pumps & Valves,Pumps & Valves
        About the Company
        ACME Engineering Industries have been Manufacturer and Exporter of mechanical steel and
        pumps since 1985. We are serving more than 15 countries around the world, including USA, UK,
        Germany, Canada, Australia, African Region, Asia etc. We have more than 20,000 Sq. Feet space for
        manufacturing facility having state of the art CNC Machines to manufacture quality products. To
        assure the quality, we have well equipped quality department with qualified and experienced man
        power.  Our product line consists of Component Mechanical seal, Cartridge Seal, Magnetic Drive
        Chemical Process Pumps (up to 60HP), SS Lobe pump and Gear Pump.


                                                               Stand No.I-145
        AIRA 4MATIC GLOBAL VALVE
        AUTOMATION PVT LTD
        Addl Plot No. 174, Shivshakti Estate, Near Prince Hotel
        Ahemdabad-79,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-79-29999239
        E-mail                    :   info@4maticvalves.com
        Website                   :   www.4maticvalves.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Zaheen Muzammil, Director
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Tapan Dave, Marketing Manage
                                     Mr. Zaheen Muzammil, Director
        Range of Products         :   Pumps & Valves
        Quality Certification     :  ISO, API
        About  the Company:  We’re  an  export  oriented  BALL,GATE,GLOBE,NRV,CONTROL
        VALVES, manufacturing facility based in India. We have been established and prominent company
        with an excellent track record in Engineered Valves &  Automation  within. We have never
        compromise in quality and services to our valued patrons. We believe in keeping patrons happy by
        providing our products at highly competitive rates. We have excellent team who guides with best
        ideas to your process solutions. Our product details are shared here which will help you to source
        the desired way. We have clear past in different applications in process industries.
                                                                           27]]></page><page Index="30"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-130
        ALFA SWITCHGEAR (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED

        No.27, Moolakkarai Road, Sithan Kuttai Backside,
        Sithan Kuttai Backside, Erode-638107, Tamil Nadu, India
        Tel                       :   91-424--2555616
        E-mail                    :   alfa@alfaswitchgear.com
        Website                   :   www.alfaswitchgear.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. V. S. Elango
                                     Ms. E. Jayageetha
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. V. S. Elango, Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        About the Company
        Alfa Switchgear India Pvt Ltd carries 33 years of success story behind its current unique identity
        among the largest manufacturers of high voltage panel boards that meet international standards.
        We are contractors and manufacturers of electrical panel boards upto 36 KV . ABB  Panel Builder
        among the globe.  We export our products to Sri Lanka, Saudi Arabia, Kenya, Nigeria, Tanzania,
        Madagascar, Togo & Benin and South africa. The CEO of Alfa switchgear, Engineer Mr. Elango
        being a humanist, he maintains harmony, understanding, transparency and discipline among the
        employees. He was felicitated with the most prestigious Gem of India award.


                                                              Stand No.I-199d
        AMI ENTERPRISES PVT.LTD.

        C-68, Phase-II, Adityapur Indl. Area,
        Jamshedpur-832109,Jharkhand, India
        Tel                       :   91-657 2200525
        E-mail                    :   info@amiglobal.in
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Chandrakant Zatakia
                                     Ms. Varsha Chandrakant Zatakia
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Deenanath Pandey, Senior Manager
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel
        Countries of Export       :   Bhutan, Germany, Kuwait, Malaysia,
                                     Oman, Saudi Arabia, UAE,Zambia
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001 : 2015
        About the Company :  We are a leding name in the Oxygen Lancing Pipe & Thermal Lancing
        Pipe throughout the country as well as overseas with almost all the  Steel, Ferro Alloys, Zinc &
        Copper producer as it's customer. The company has a well established name in the entire country as
        well as African and Middle-East countries. Our main products are  various type of Conveyor Idler
        Rollers as per the customer's requirement, Oxygen Lancing Pipe, Thermal Lancing Pipe, Tubes for
        use in  LPG  Cylinders and Automotive Industires etc.


         28]]></page><page Index="31"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-199B
        ANSHUMAN TECH PVT LTD

        Plot No. 13, Sthairya Society,, Behind Tol Hospital,
        Near Navsahyadri Chowk, Pune-411052, Maharashtra, India
        Tel                       :   91-20-25460892
        Fax                       :   91-20-25463052
        E-mail                    :   account@anshumantech.net
        Website                   :   www.anshumantech.net
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Rajeev Patil
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Amol Mansukh Jangam
                                     Sr. Customer Support Engineer
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        About the Company: Anshuman Tech is a Manufacture & Exporter of Technical, Electronic
        & Educational Trainer Kits, Instruments, Laboratory Training Equipment & many more similar
        products. Anshuman work in close contact with clients to produce user friendly products & manuals
        providing a fulfilling teaching & learning experience. A strong service support team guarantee
        complete satisfaction for the customer.




































                                                                           29]]></page><page Index="32"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-163
        ANG EXIM LLP
        111 - A, Premsons Industrial Estate, Caves Road,
        Mumbai-400060,Maharashtra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22-28396019, 982080

        E-mail                    :   akash@angexim.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Akash Shah
        & Participant                Designated Partner
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components, Agricultural
                                     Machinery & Equipment, Pumps &
                                     Valves
        Countries of Export       :   Kenya, Mozambique, Zambia
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001: 2015
        About the Company : We introduce ourselves as Exporters of Automobile and Agriculture
        Spare Parts for East African countries like Kenya, Tanzania , Zambia, Egypt, Sudan, South Africa,
        etc, we also develop custom made items & specialise in reverse engineering for our clients.




                                                              Stand No. I-159
        ASSOMAC MACHINES LIMITED
        546, Bisrakh Road,Chappraula Dist. , Gautam Budh Nagar
        Ghaziabad,Dadri-201009, Uttar Pradesh, India

        Tel                       :   91-120-9810075965, 98102975
        E-mail                    :   nirmalsingh@assomac.in
        Website                   :   www.assomacmachines.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Nirmal Singh
        & Participant                Director

        Range of Products         :   Wire Drawing Machines, Wire Cutting
                                     Machinery, Wire Making Machinery
        About the Company:  The ASSOMAC Group has established itself as one of India’s leading
        names in the field of Wire Drawing Machines, Wire Cutting Machinery, Wire Making Machinery
        with our promise of quality products that stay ahead of time. The ASSOMAC Group of Companies
        is an integrated conglomerate of engineering companies  engaged in manufacturing all types
        equipment and the accessories used in making Alloy Steel, Carbon Steel, Mild Steel, Stainless Steel
        and other Non-Ferrous Wires.


         30]]></page><page Index="33"><![CDATA[31]]></page><page Index="34"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-135
        ATLAS MACHINES (INDIA)
        20, Ambalal Doshi Marg, Hamam Street, Fort, Mumbai-400001, Maharashtra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22-66359900
        E-mail                    :   gurpreetsingh@atlasmachinesindia.com
        Website                   :   www.atlasmachinesindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Jaswant Singh Soni
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Gurpreet Singh Soni, Partner
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment,
                                     Sawing & Cutting Machinery, Welding Tools &
                                     Equipment,Construction & Earthmoving Machinery
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001-2015 Certified Company
        About the Company:  Atlas Machines (India), came into existence in 1975 with the soul
        aim of catering to the most quality conscious buyers of Machines & Plants. At the helm of the
        affairs, 47yrs of hands-on experience the company has acquired un-parallel expertise in the field
        of Exports of Machines, Machine Tools & Accessories and now is one of the best in its field. By
        serving the Government Undertakings - MNC's - Technical Colleges, Sugar Factories - Small
        Scale Workshops across the globe,  we look forward to serve you as we serve them with the same
        fervor. Visit Us At: www.atlasmachinesindia.com


                                                               Stand No.I-116
        BEML LIMITED

        Flat No. E, F, G, H, 11th Floor Vandana Building,
        Tolstoy Marg, New Delhi-110001, India
        Tel                       :   91-9820161804
        E-mail                    :   mx@beml.co.in
        Website                   :   www.bemlindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executives  :   Mr. M. V. Rajasekha
                                     Mr. Ajit Kumar Srivastav; Mr. Anil Jerath
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Ajeet Pratap Srivastava, Deputy General Manager
                                     Mr. B. Saktmivel Murugan, Manager
        Range of Products         :   Mining Equipment & Machinery,
                                     Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        About the Company : BEML Limited established in 1964, is a leading multi-technology and
        multi-location company under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India offering high-quality
        products for diverse sectors of economy such as Coal, Mining, Steel, Cement, Power, Irrigation,
        Construction, Road Building, Defense & Aerospace, Railway & Metro etc.  BEML has exported
        more than 1300 units of Mining & Construction Equipment worth about US$ 300 million to
        more than 68 countries of various continents.  BEML operates in three business verticals - Mining
        & Construction, Rail & Metro and Defence.  The various products manufactured include Dozers,
        Excavators, Loaders, Treasury Vans and many more.
         32]]></page><page Index="35"><![CDATA[33]]></page><page Index="36"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-171
        BRAHMANI ENTERPRISE

        16 Bhaktinagar Station Plot,
        Rajkot-360002, Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-281-8000153222
        E-mail                    :   brahmanienterprise@ymail.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Bharatbhai Manjibhai
                                     Sagpariya
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Yagnik Bharatbhai Sagpariya
                                     Diploma Mech. Engg.
        Range of Products         :   Aluminum and Products made of
                                     Aluminium, Building Material
        About  the Company :  We are Brahmani Enterprise and was founded in year 1995 and we
        manufacturing Architechtural Hardware products like Cabinet Handle, Main Door Handle, Tower
        Bolts etc. and we are manufacturing in metals like Aluminium, Brass, Steel and Zinc etc. and now
        we are only suppling in various cities in India and we are doing all in house machining process.
        Our moto is to serve the best quality products with best rates.
        We have wide range of products as well as we have wide range of finishes.



































         34]]></page><page Index="37"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-175
        DAGA POLYLAMINATORS PVT LTD

        G-643-646 & E-277-277(A/1) and E-277-277A, Marudhar Industrial Area,
        Iind Phase Basni Jodhpur (East)-342006, Rajasthan, India
        Tel                       :   91-291-2745805
        Fax                       :   91-291-2746855
        E-mail                    :   jodmetal@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.dagafoil.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Sandeep Daga
                                     Mr. Pradeep Daga
                                     Mr. Devendra Daga
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Sandeep Daga, Director
                                     Mr. Pradeep Daga, Director
        Range of Products         :   Aluminium and Products made of Aluminium
        Countries of Export       :   Bangladesh, Ethiopia, Ghana,Kenya, Philippines,
                                     Sri Lanka,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001-2015
        About the Company: Manufacturer of Coated ,Laminated  and Printed Aluminium Foil Anf
        Flexible Laminates for Pharmaceutical and Food Packaging and Lidding Foil for Packaging of
        Food, Cosmetics and Dairy Products.
                                                              Stand No. I-124
        DEPROCON CONTROLS

        Attur Layout, Bangalore-560106, Karnataka, India
        Tel                       :   91-9972097991
        E-mail                    :   deprocon.controls@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.deprocon.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Udaykumar
        & Participant                CEO
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Indonesia, Iran, Nigeria, Uganda,
                                     Zambia
        Quality Certification     :  ISO9001, ISO140001
        About  the Company :  Deprocon  is  an MSME unit located in Bangalore specialized
        in  Control, Protection  &  Automation  Systems upto 400kV Deprocon  is  an ISO 9001
        certified  company,  professionally  managed and  was  started  in  2006,this  has  over  a  decade
        of experience in designing, manufacturing and installing panels for complex power systems
        Deprocon has been receiving repeat orders from clients in Zambia, Nigeria, Uganda which vouches
        for the quality and competency of Deprocon Team. We have in house competency in programming
        Numerical relays of various makes as well as customizing the automation systems using RTU/
        SCADA.

                                                                           35]]></page><page Index="38"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-151
        DGC INDUSTRIES PRIVATE LIMITED
        Plot No. 46, Pocket F,, Sector - 4, DSIDC Indl. Area, Bawana
        Delhi-110039, India
        Tel                       :   91-7834856000
        E-mail                    :   dipendholakiya@dgc.co.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Dipen Dholakiya
        & Participant                Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components
        About the Company: Manufacturers of Rubber Parts & Plastic Injection Body Parts for passenger
        cars. Manufacturers of Plastic Injection Body Parts such as Bumpers, Grills, Radiator Supports,
        Inner fenders etc & Sheet Metal Bonded Rubber Parts such as Bushings, Mounts, Strut Kits etc .
        & Exporter of Genuine Spare Parts for Korean Japanese American cars











































         36]]></page><page Index="39"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-143

        ECOSURE PULPMOLDING TECHNOLOGIES LTD
        Plot No. 92, Udyog Kendra, Ecotech-III Gautam Buddha Nagar,
        Greater Noida - 201306 (U.P.), Uttar Pradesh, India
        Tel                       :   91-918447821460
        E-mail                    :   robert_leslie@ecosurepulpmolding.in
        Website                   :   www.ecosurepulpmolding.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Mohit Kumar
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Robert Leslie Malonga, Sales Engineer Export
                                     Mr. Mohit Kumar, Co-Founder
        Range of Products         :   Packaging Machinery
        About the Company:  We are a team of professionals with vast experience in pulp, packaging and
        machinery manufacturing both in domestic and international markets. 100% Made In India. We are
        offering solutions available right from sourcing of raw material to finished goods. All machines &
        equipment are made in India sourced & fabricated indigenously. Converting Non-wood fiber into
        Food grade pulp suitable for molded wares. We are focused on sustainable utilization of agriculture
        materials for products that benefit rural communities and consumers. Agriculture feed stocks, both
        dedicated crops and residues, provide key building blocks for an array of products.


                                                              Stand No. I-162
        ELECTRONIC AUTOMATION PRIVATE LIMITED
        No.20, KHB Industrial Area, Yelahanka
        Bangalore-560064, Karnataka, India
        Tel                       :   91-80-42802345
        E-mail                    :   sales@eaplindiamail.com
        Website                   :   www.eaplindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Ashok L Shanbhag
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Venugopal Thalpanaje Sharma
                                     Sales Executive
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   UAE
        Quality Certification     :  CE,CSA
        About the Company : EAPL had its humble beginning in the year 1985. It was the brainchild of
        Late Shri Madhav Kamat, who instituted this venture with espousing support from Mr. Christian
        Kruger of Switzerland. By launching A1D1 – X, EAPL has established itself as a stronghold for in-
        house manufacturing of standard electronic instruments. As opposed to heavy material instruments,
        EAPL designs and develops a multitude of compact versions that ensure efficient and optimum
        level functioning of process control.


                                                                           37]]></page><page Index="40"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-149
        FERTIPLANT ENGINEERING CO PVT LTD
        2nd Floor, Moray House, 226 S. V. Road, Bandra West,
        Mumbai-400050, Maharashtra, India

        Tel                       :   91-99203 22331
        E-mail                    :   sanjeev.doshi@fertiplant.in
        Website                   :   www.fertiplant.in
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Sanjeev Ramesh Deshmukh
                                     Mr. Samir Sharad Deshmukh
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Samir Deshmukh, Director
                                     Mr. Sanjeev Doshi, Director
        Range of Products         :   Material Handling Equipment
        About the Company: Fertiplant  Engineering is a 55+ year old company, giving know-how,
        engineering and supply of complete NPK granulation plant to cover mechanical and electrical
        equipment  and  instruments  and  control systems.  More  than  60 plants  have  been  installed  in
        India and 6 plants overseas. As all mechanical equipment are manufactured in-house, Fertiplant
        has  expertise  in  all material handling equipment, like Belt Conveyors, Weigh Feeders, Bucket
        Elevators,  Crushers, Vibrating  Screens  etc.  Rotary equipment  like  Dryers  and  Coolers  and
        Kilns  and calciners  also form a major part of their  expertise  and so  do grinding  ball mills.
                                                              Stand No.B170b
        FRONTIER TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED

        Narsinghpur, Gurgaon-122004, Haryana, India
        Tel                       :   91-124-6513331
        E-mail                    :   aditya.saigal@frontec.co.in
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Ashok Saigal
                                     Mr. Aditya Saigal
                                     Mr. Vickram Saigal
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Aditya Saigal
                                     Director
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Austria, Brazil, China, Kenya,
                                     Netherlands,Zambia
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About  the Company :  Frontec manufactures heat shrink tubing, moulded shapes and cable
        jointing kits.  HS cable jointing kits are in use in all parts of India by utilities and leading electrical
        contractor for over 25 years.  Heat Shrink Components are regularly private branded and exported
        to European buyers since early 2000's.  Cable Jointing Kits and Accessories have been supplied
        to African  countries.  These are type tested to Indian Standards which are equivalent to IEC
        requirements.

         38]]></page><page Index="41"><![CDATA[Stand No.B194b
        G K XIANGHE ELECTRICALS PVT LTD

        D-4, Phase-II, New Mandideep Industrial Area, Bhopal-462023, Madhya Pradesh, India
        Tel                       :   91-755-2586160
        E-mail                    :   sales3@gkinsulator.com
        Website                   :   www.gkinsulator.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Hemant Jangalwa
                                     Mr. Ramesh Jangalwa
                                     Ms. Kalpana Jangalwa
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Kunal Jangalwa, Marketing Head (Exports)
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Benin, Ethiopia, Ghana, Kenya, Nigeria,
                                     Rwanda, Tanzania,Toga
        Quality Certification     :  ISO-9001
        About  the  Company:  GK Xianghe is a leading manufacturer of Silicon Rubber Composite
        Insulators in India, ranging from 11kV to 1200kV. GK Xianghe Pvt Ltd is a joint venture project
        formed in 2007, by the promoters of GK Electricals, an Indian partnership firm and Zhengzhou
        Xianghe Group Electric Manufacturing Company Limited, a state owned company from the
        People’s Republic of China. GK Xianghe is an ISO-9001 certified company and all the products
        manufactured have been type tested with internationally approved laboratories.
                                                               Stand No.I-112
        GI AGRO TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LTD
        33 Self Help Industrial Estate, Baliga Road, Keelkattalai,
        Chennai-600117,Tamil Nadu, India

        Tel                       :   91-44-9444046801
        E-mail                    :   info@giagrotech.com
        Website                   :   www.giagrotech.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Arunachalam Sharathi
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Arunachalam Sharathi
                                     Director
                                     Mr. P Surianarayanan
                                     Project Manager
        Range of Products         :   Food Processing Machinery
        About  the Company :  Leading Manufacturer of entire range of Cashew Nut processing
        machinery, provide turn key project and project consultancy to establish Plants in India and Africa .





                                                                           39]]></page><page Index="42"><![CDATA[40]]></page><page Index="43"><![CDATA[41]]></page><page Index="44"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-199
        GOVERNMENT OF JHARKHAND
        Nepal House, Ranchi,  Jharkhand
        Ranchi-834002, Jharkhand, India


        Tel                       :   91-651-2491844
        E-mail                    :   jhr-doi@nic.in
        Website                   :   www.jharkhand.gov.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Jitendra Kumar Singh,
        & Participant                Director, Industries
        Range of Products         :   Government Body
        About the Company :
        Department of Industries, Government of Jharkhand, works to create an investor friendly
        environment & improve ease of doing business in Jharkhand








                                                               Stand No.I-165
        HARSH PRANJAL INSTRUMENT & POWER PRIVATE LIMITED
        Sophistica D-0805, Casa Bella Gold, Kalyan Shill Road Dombivli,
        Thane-421204, Maharashtra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22-8850922364
        E-mail                    :   info@hpinstrumentpower.com
        Website                   :   www.hpinstrumentpower.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Runesh Kamalakar Ghadi
                                     Mr. Pradeep Kumar Sinha
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Prashant Kumar, Partner
                                     Mr. Pradeep Ganpat Katalkar, Partner
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment, Pumps & Valves,Wire
                                     & Cables,Heating,  Ventilation, Air Conditioning &
                                     Refrigeration (HVAC-R), Articles of Iron & Steel
        Countries of Export       :   Jordan,Nigeria,United Arab Emirates
        About  the Company :  Harsh Pranjal (HP)  Instrument & Power Pvt. Ltd., is  a registered company in
        Mumbai in India. We are the team of professionals who understand the customer needs and try to fulfill those
        requirements in appropriate span of time with suitable price.  We have a complete range of Instrumentation &
        Electrical products starting from Multimeters, Gauges, Transmitters, Gas Analyzers, Thermocouples, Switches,
        Control Valve & Accessories, Vibration Monitoring System, Electrical Measuring Instruments, Breakers, Fuses,
        MCBs, Cables, Mechanical items like Seals, Bearings, Mechanical valves, Pumps, shaft and Gas Turbines Spare
        Parts. Overhauling of Turbines & Compressors, Electrical Projects, Urea Reactor Leak Detection System
         42]]></page><page Index="45"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-154
        HIMALAYA MACHINERY PVT LTD
        601,GIDC, Makarpura Indstrial Area,
        Vadodara-390010,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-265-2643224
        Fax                       :   91-265-2638778
        E-mail                    :   info@himalayamachine.com
        Website                   :   www.himalayamachine.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Rohan Shah
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Vanaamudan Jayabal,  Client Success Manager
        Range of Products         :   Pharmaceutical Machinery
        About the Company : Himalaya is producing quality Plate Bending /  Straightening / Levelling
        Machines for more than four decades. The very first machine built four decades ago is working
        satisfactorily. We so far have supplied more than 3000 machines from our range in various parts
        of India and abroad as well. We have executed more than 400+ repeat orders from our satisfied
        customers. Big corporate companies like; Tata, Birla, Thermax, L&T, UB Group, Godrej, Voltas,
        Kirloskar, Alfa-Laval, Reliance etc, are among our many valued clients in India.  Our foreign
        installations are in Gulf countries, Russia, Indonesia, Singapore, Sri Lanka, Uganda, Kenya etc.


                                                             Stand No.-B170a
        HIRANI AUTOMOTIVE INDUSTRIES

        Surve No.24/1, Plot No.2, Shapar Main Road, Opp. Rajkot Oil Cake,
        Rajkot-360021,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-281-2827-252667
        E-mail                    :   info@omxsupension.com
        Website                   :   www.omxsuspension.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Nirbhay Hirani, MD
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Nirbhay Hirani, MD
                                     Mr. Mayur Hirani, MD
                                     Mr. Deepak Mehta, Manager
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components
        Countries of Export       :   Algeria, Nigeria, Sri Lanka,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company : With 23 Years of experience in Automobile Products, we, “Hirani Automotive
        Industries”, are a coveted manufacturers, suppliers, and exporter of Automotive Suspension  &
        Supportive Systems and Automotive Pulleys. We are an association firm and are situated at Rajkot,
        (Gujarat, India). Our range is fabricated utilizing premium quality crude material that we get from
        solid and dependable merchants of the market. Our organization is a member of the highly famed
        CII & EEPC.
                                                                           43]]></page><page Index="46"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-148
        HOOGHLY ALLOY AND STEELS CO PVT LTD

        90, Stephen House, 4 BBD Bag East
        Kolkata-700001,West Bengal, India
        Tel                       :   91-33-22424278
        E-mail                    :   chanchalgos@gmail.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Prem Kumar Agarwal
                                     Mr. Ashok Kumar Agarwal
                                     Mr. Prateek Agarwal
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Chanchal Goswami, Executive Director
        Range of Products         :   Structural Steel Items like, Angles
                                     Channels, Beams, Ferro Silicon, Silico Manganese
        Countries of Export       :   Bangladesh, Ghana, Sri Lanka,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO-9001
        About the Company : We are a leading manufacturer Exporter of Structural Steel items like,
        Mild Steel Angles, Channels and Beams. We are an ISO -9001 organization and maintain very high
        quality standards. Ours plant is equipped with State-of-the-Art technology and equipment. Our
        overseas customers are fully satisfied with the quality and shipment schedules of our supplies. We are
        totally committed to the standard of quality of our product. We are proud to announce that we have
        been receiving the Star Performance Awards for Exports from EEPC. We are a Star Export House.

                                                               Stand No.I-160
        HTC VALVES PRIVATE LIMITED

        614, G.I.D.C., National Highway No-8, Ranoli
        Vadodara-391350,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-9023732126
        E-mail                    :   ankur.panchal@htcvalves.com
        Website                   :   www.htcvalves.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Hemal Pandya
                                     Ms. Jyotsna Pandya
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Ankur Panchal, International Sales Manager
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        About the Company : Over 50+ types of Industrial Valve manufacturer & 33+ years of valve
        maintenance expertise, we have built an enviable client base in India and supply over 30,000
        valves every year. We have also supplied our products in countries like Congo – Africa and Saudi
        Arabia. Kindly refer below link to reference orders from our valuable clients. • Control Valves •
        Process Ball valves • Flanged & Wafer type Butterfly valves • Pressure Safety Valves  • Plug Valves  •
        Gate, Globe & Check Valves • Lined Valves, Pipes & Fittings • Actuators • Knife Edge Gate Valves
        • Customized Valves.



         44]]></page><page Index="47"><![CDATA[45]]></page><page Index="48"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-161
        HYDROPOWER TECH ENGINEERING

        Behind Yogeshwar Ind.Area, Plot No.1, Survey No. 206/4/1,
        Ne Ar Almighty, Ravki Kankot Road, Ravki, Rajkot-360021, Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-281-9638888634
        E-mail                    :   hydraulicpressmfg@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.hptironworker.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Rupesh Amreliya
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Rupesh Amreliya,Managing Director
                                     Mr. Arjun Parsana, Sales Executive
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment,
                                     Construction & Earthmoving, Machinery,Material
                                     Handling Equipment, Mining Equipment &
                                     Machinery, Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Kenya, Nepal, Oman, Sri Lanka, Uganda,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO, CE
        About the Company : Established in the year 2009, we, “Hydro Power Tech Engineering”, are
        counted among the prominent Manufacturer, Exporter and Trader engaged in offering our clients
        with a commendable range of Iron Worker Machines, Cutting Machines, Punching Machines, etc.
        At our premises, we manufacture these machines with the aid of modern tools and technology,
        installed at our infrastructure facility. Apart from this, to cater to the exact demands of customers,
        we work in close coordination with them.
                                                              Stand No. I-123
        IMPRESS APPAREL MACHINES PVT LTD

        No. 91/2A, Hongasandra, Begur Main Road
        Bangalore-560068, Karnataka, India
        Tel                       :   91-99886209330
        Fax                       :   91-80- 25742648
        E-mail                    :   impressindia@hotmail.com
        Website                   :   www.sublimationindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Srinath H N,
        & Participant                Director
        Range of Products         :   Printing Machinery
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company: Established in 2006, Impress Apparel Machines Private Limited is engaged
        in manufacturing of Fusing, apparel printing, sublimation printing, lanyard printing , die cutting and
        co related equipment.  We have achieved expertise in catering to the requirements of our clients
        exactly as per their specifications. We emphasize on stringent quality standards in order to ensure
        that the products provided to our clients is always optimum to its level. we are a  company with
        over 2 decades of experience and are serving the best companies in India like Jockey, Gokuldas, Gus
        Clothing, Arvind Fashions  and many companies are being served by us.


         46]]></page><page Index="49"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-179
        KAY BOUVET ENGINEERING LTD

        N-3, Additional MIDC Area, Satara-415004, Maharastra, India
        Tel                       :   91-2162-2162 240653
        Fax                       :   91-20162-240653
        E-mail                    :   aditi.chandra@kaybouvet.com
        Website                   :   www.kaybouvet.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Niraj Chandra
        Name of the Participants   :   Ms. Aditi Chandra, Executive Director
                                     Mr. Carlos Gomez Legaspi,
                                     Business Development Manager
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel, Food Processing
                                     Machinery, Material Handling
                                     Equipment, Agricultural Machinery &
                                    Equipment
        About the Company : Kay Bouvet Engineering is a heavy engineering company manufacturing
        equipment for various industries like sugar mills, oil & gas, agro processing, nuclear power, aerospace
        and defence. With more than 40 years of experience in heavy engineering, Kay Bouvet has executed
        large scale projects in Africa and around the world. The company is currently executing a 2500TCD
        sugar plant for the Govt. of Tanzania on a turnkey basis. Kay Bouvet has also established a dedicated
        manufacturing facility in Tanzania becoming a one-stop solution for all engineering needs in East
        Africa.
                                                               Stand No.I-180
        LEGION EXIM LLP

        D 21, Galaxy Town Homes, Near Collector Office,
        Shroff Road, Rajkot-360001,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-8487992496
        E-mail                    :   dishant@legionexim.com
        Website                   :   www.legionexim.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Dishant Shah
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Dishant Shah, Designated Partner
                                     Mr. Shrey Javia, Designated Partner
        Range of Products         :   Pumps & Valves, Building Material, Food
                                     Processing Machinery
        About the Company : Legion Exim LLP is a merchant exporter and sourcing agent from India.
        Being strategically located in Rajkot, Gujarat - India, a significant engineering & manufacturing hub,
        enables us to source and procure internationally accredited and recognized engineering products.
        The company's promoters have vast experience in manufacturing pumps, valves, and refractories
        as well as international trade and supply chain expertise. The deep network and connections of the
        company and its promoters facilitate trusted transactions seamlessly between the manufacturers and
        international buyers & importers. The company primarily believes in building trust and conviction
        between all the parties involved in the trade.

                                                                           47]]></page><page Index="50"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-153
        INDIA AGROVISION IMPLEMENTS PVT LTD

        G-1/11 RIICO Industrial Area,Udyog Vihar,  Jaitpura,
        Chomu,  Jaipur-303704, Rajasthan, India
        Tel                       :   91-992905 2289, 96364943
        E-mail                    :   info@indiaagrovision.com
        Website                   :   www.indiaagrovision.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Ram Swaroop Jangid
                                     Ms. Narangi Devi
                                     Mr. Ajay Kumar Jangid
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Ashok Jangid, Director
                                     Mr. Govind Sharma,Advisor to Director
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment
        Quality Certification     :  ISO, OHSAS and CE CERTIFIED
        About  the Company :  India Agrovision  Implements  Private  Limited.  Established  in  2010,
        engaged in the manufacturing & exporting of Agricultural Farm Machines under the brand name
        AGROVISION. We are a 100% Export Company and A Government of India recognized Star
        Export House. The company`s diverse range of products includes Rotary Tillers, Disc Harrows,
        Disc Ploughs, Disc Ridgers, Tyne Ridgers, Tipping & Non-Tipping Trailers, Spring Loaded Tillers,
        Box Blades, Grader Blade, Seed Planters, Sugar Cane Loader, Rigid Tillers, Land Levellers, Post
        Hole Diggers, Sub Soilers, Rotary Slashers, Reciprocating Bar Mowers, etc. marked by more than
        50 years of experience.
































         48]]></page><page Index="51"><![CDATA[49]]></page><page Index="52"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-129
        INDUSTRIAL BOILERS LTD

        225-1B, 226, 227, 228,Vapi Industrial Township, GIDC, Vapi-396195,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-260-9712940248
        E-mail                    :   zaraan@indboilers.com
        Website                   :   www.indboilers.com
        Name of the Chief Executives    :   Ms. Homai R. Engineer
                                     Mr. Rohinton R. Engineer; Mr. Cyrus Engineer
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Zaraan Engineer, President-Operations
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel
        Countries of Export       :   Bangladesh, Bhutan, Ghana, Iraq, Kenya, Laos, Malawi,
                                     Malaysia, Mozambique, Myanmar,Nepal,New
                                     Zealand, Nigeria Poland, Romainia, Russia,Saudi Arabia,
                                     Singapore, South Africa,Sri Lanka, Tanzania,Thailand,
                                     Uganda, UAE,Vietnam,Zambia
        Quality Certification     :   ISO 9001:2015 ; A.S.M.E.; CE-EUROCERT; I.B.R.
        About the Company: Industrial  Boilers  Ltd. an acknowledged leader in the Boiler Industry, having
        ISO 9001:2015 Accredited; CE-Certified;ASME Authorised  Company, that  delivers  total technical
        engineering solutions, from its  2 units  in Vapi having total area of more than 30,000  Sq. Mtrs, to
        challenging problems in the areas of Energy, Steam, Power and Environment. We  produce  a  range  of
        world- class Boilers, viz. Oil-Fired ; Multi-fuel ; Agrowaste , Waste –To–Energy solutions, incorporating
        State–of - Art technology.  Steam Turbines & Co-generation  equipments  are  manufactured  by  our
        wholly owned subsidiary -  IB Turbo Pvt. Ltd., at Noida   Website: http://www.indboilers.com
                                                               Stand No.I-141
        JEYALETSHMI MACHINE WORKS
        114 D, Sathy Road, Viswasapuram, Saravanampatty,Coimbatore-641035,Tamil Nadu, India
        Tel                       :   91-422-2666586
        E-mail                    :   nandagopal@jmwindia.com
        ebsite                    :   www.jmwindia.com
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Kalyanasundaram Nandagopal, Partner
                                     Mr. Kulandaivelu Srinivasan,Marketing Manager
        Range of Products         :   Plastic Machinery
        Countries of Export       :   Algeria, Bangladesh,Denmark, Egypt,Ethiopia, Germany,
                                     Indonesia, Kenya,  Nepal, Nigeria, Saudi Arabia, South
                                     Africa, Sri Lanka,Sudan, Thailand,Tunisia,UAE,Vietnam
                                     Zambia
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About the Company : Established in 1984 JMW has positioned itself from the beginning leader
        in manu-facturing of Heavy Duty Ring Twisters and Online Ring Winders. JMW machineries
        are used for producing Multifold Cotton, Synthetic HDPE and PP  Twines that in turn used in
        Sewing Threads, Bag Closing Thread, Carpet Yarn, Jute Twine, Fishnet Twine etc with more than
        1000 installation in India. Every year we export 40% of our machineries to country such as Kenya,
        Nigeria, Saudi Arabia, Germany, Ludhiana, Vietnam, Thailand, Bangldesh, Sri Lanka etc., Product:
        Ring Doubler, Medium and Heavy Ring Twister for Ply and Cabling, Online Ring Winders.
         50]]></page><page Index="53"><![CDATA[51]]></page><page Index="54"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-122
        LPR EXPORTS ENGINE COMPONENTS PVT LTD

        Mathura Road, Artoni, Agra-282007, Uttar Pradesh, India
        Tel                       :   91-98370 06940
        E-mail                    :   arunlprexports@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.lprexports.com
        Name of the Chief Executive    :   Mr. Arun Luthra
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Arun Luthra, Director
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components,Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning
                                     & Refrigeration  (HVAC-R),Articles of Iron & Steel,
                                     Aluminium and Products made of Aluminium,
                                     Construction & Earthmoving Machinery
        Countries of Export       :   Belarus, Brazil, Egypt,Germany,  Italy,  Malaysia,Mexico,
                                     Netherlands, Peru, Spain, UAE, UK, USA,Vietnam
        Quality Certification     :   ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company: We are the Manufacturers and Exporters of Engine and Compressor Components
        Piston Rings ,Cylinder Liners ,  Air Cooled Blocks,Pistons, Bronze Bushes, Connecting Rods,Oil
        Pumps,Crankshafts, Safety Valves made of Brass, Rubber & Teflon Parts, Bearings and Bushes, Machined
        and Cast Components, Forgings ,Parts Made of Iron and Steel, Aluminium Components Made by PDC or
        Gravity or Forging , Parts for Deisel Staionery and Moving Engines & Generators, Air Brake Compressor
        Kits,  Parts  for  Earth  Moving  Equipments,  Industrial  Refrigeration  Compressor  Parts    and  parts  for Air
        Conditioning Compressors HVAC, Parts for Industrial Air Compressors and  Pnuematic and Hydraulic
        Assemblies,
                                                               Stand No.I-169
        M L TOOLS INDUSTRIES
        7-3-109/B/1 Madhubhan Colony,Gagan Pahad
        Hyderabad-500077,Telangana, India
        Tel                       :   91-9849030551
        E-mail                    :   mltoolshyd@hotmail.com
        Website                   :   www.powertextools.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Laxmi Narayan Gupta
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Laxmi Narayan Gupta, Proprietor
                                     Mr. Ashwin Kumar Kalantri, Manager
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment, Building Material,
                                     Construction &  Earthmoving Machinery,Hand Tools &
                                     Power Tools,Mining Equipment & Machinery
        About the Company : Powertex is a brand which is loved by its customers,because of its wide
        range of  products  along with  world class  quality.  Powertex  specialized  in  products  like  Power
        Tools,Garden Tools,Car Washers etc. qualitity of spares is much better than any other brand with in
        this range available in Indian market. In the very short time the Powertex has won many hearts of
        the customers,our major motive is to provide best service in terms of cost and quality and which
        gives value for money.




         52]]></page><page Index="55"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-111
        MAG HARD INSULATORS
        B-102, Parsian Apartment, Opp., Fidai Baug,
        V.P. Road,, Andheri (W), Mumbai-400058, Maharashtra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22-26235272
        E-mail                    :   info@maghardinsulators.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Manan Suresh Doshi,
        & Participant               Proprietor
        Range of Products         :   Aluminium and products made of Aluminum,Wire &
                                     Cables,Heating,  Ventilation, Air Conditioning &
                                     Refrigeration (HVAC-R),Building Material
        Countries of Export       :   Kenya, Nigeria, Qatar, Sierra Leone, Thailand,
                                     Uganda, United Arab Emirates
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About the Company : We are pleased to introduce ourselves as one of the leading Thermal
        Insulation Material Manufacturers, Suppliers and Applicators, having a track record of successfully
        catering to almost all types of industries viz. Chemicals, Fertilizers, Textiles, Sugar, Cement and
        Petrochemical Industries, for more than 4 decades in India.We also supply following material:
        Glasswool, Ceramic Wool,Nitrile Rubber,Calcium Silicate,and many more.Manufacturing of
        Rigid Polyurethane Foam Sheets & Pipe Sections and Pipe Supports. We are Exporter of all kind
        of Insulation materials & overseas Insulation Contractor. We also undertake Turnkey Insulation
        Jobs of any magnitude and any location.
                                                               Stand No.I-137
        MAGCORE LAMINATION (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED
        111-A, Bommasandra Industrial, Area, Anekal Taluk,
        Bangalore-560099,Karnataka, India
        Tel                       :   91-80-27832053
        Fax                       :   91-080-41667376
        E-mail                    :   info@magcore.in
        Website                   :   www.magcore.in
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Babulal P Bhansali
                                     Mr. Vikram Kumar Bhansali ; Ms. Umadevi  Bhansali
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Babulal P Bhansali, Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Electrical Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   American Samoa,Australia,Germany, Indonesia, Kuwait,
                                     Norway,Oman, Turkey,United Arab Emirates
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About  the Company:  One of the major supplier for Electrical Rotating Machinery Parts
        supplier viz. Electrical Laminations for Stator Stack, Die Casted Rotor, for different applications.
        size 50 mm diameter to 1200 mm in a single Blow , Segmental Stamping for higher diameter >
        1200 mm 1) Engineering Industry 2) White Goods - Table Fan, Ceiling Fan, Mixie, Power Tools
        3) Electric Vehicles  4) Alternators /  Wind Generator / Hydro Generator 5) Traction Motors We
        have infrastructure to manufacture dia 500mm x length 800mm
                                                                           53]]></page><page Index="56"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-164
        MAKSON MACHINERY PVT. LTD.
        3-Kumbharpara, Po Box-18
        Surendranagar-363002,Gujarat, India


        Tel                       :   91-98792 00062
        E-mail                    :  maulik8888@gmail.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Maulik Mahendrabhai Makasana
                                     Mr. Rajubhai Chaturbhai Patel
                                     Mr. Tusharbhai Chaturbhai Patel
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Maulik Mahendrabhai Makasana, Director

        Range of Products         :   Bakery & Confectionery Machinery
        About the Company:  Company product Confectionary Machine & machinery parts
        manufacturing. Like Candy, lollipop machinery







                                                               Stand No.I-140
        MARUTHI ELECTRODES PVT.LTD.

        138 5th Floor Maruthi Tower Hal Airport Road Kodihalli, Bangalore-560008,Karnataka, India
        Tel                       :   91-80-25275848
        Fax                       :   91-80-25266289
        E-mail                    :   meplfact@maruthielectrodes.com
        Website                   :   www.maruthiweld.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Gurappa Jayarama Reddy Raja
                                     Ms. Priyanka Jayarama Reddy Raja
                                     Mr. Srisailaraja
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Ramakanth Gururaj, General Manager (Ma &Mktg.)
                                     Mr. Somanathapura Venkatarayappa
                                     Nagaraja, General Manager (Finance)
        Range of Products         :   Wire & Cables,Welding Tools & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Kenya
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001 : 2015
        About the Company : We, M/s Maruthi Electrodes (P) Limited established in year 1985 an ISO 9001 :
        2015 company situated near Bengaluru is one of the leading manufacturers of well-known Complete Range of
        Welding Consumables in South India. Ours is an associate concern of Maruthi Group. We are a "ONE STOP
        CENTER"  catering    complete  range  of  welding  consumables  which  includes  Special Alloying Materials,
        Welding Machines, Welding Machines Spares & Advisory Services in association with our sister company M/s
        Maruthi Impex, Bengaluru which is a Trading Organization having Distributorship of many famous well-
        known brands of welding consumables wordwide.  We are looking smart partners globally.
         54]]></page><page Index="57"><![CDATA[55]]></page><page Index="58"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-127
        METAL AIDS INDIA
        4/1, Alankar Cinema Building,, S.V.P. Road,
        Near Petrol Pump, Mumbai- 400004, Maharastra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22-23820233
        Fax                       :   91-22-23898829
        E-mail                    :   metalaidexport@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.metalaid.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. M M Munot
        & Participant                CEO
        Range of Products         :   Building Material,Articles of Iron &  Steel,Wire &
                                     Cables,Aluminum and  Products made of
                                     Aluminum,Pumps & Valves
        Countries of Export       :   Indonesia,Iran,Japan,Jordan,Kuwait, Mexico,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015 Certified by TUV
        About the Company: Manufacturers, Exporters & Importers of Stainless Steel (in Grade  AISI
        -304, 304l, 316, 316l, 310, 310s, 321, 347 etc) Alloy Steel, Duplex  Steel, Carbon Steel in shape
        of Pipes, Tubes, Flanges, Pipe  Fittings,  Round Bar,  Bright Bars,  Angle Bar,  Flat Bar, Hex  Bar,
        Square  Bar, Sheets,  Coils,  Strip, Plates, Wire, Tie Wire, Strip Banding, Decorative Tubes / Pipe,
        Valves, Threaded Fittings, Forged Fittings etc in any size / type / grade  etc. Also specialised in high
        nickel alloys like Inconel, Monel, Titanium,  Hastalloy, Tantalum, etc  in  any  size/ type/ grade.

                                                             Stand No.-B101b
        MK LIDE AUTO CLUTCH INDUSTRIES (P) LTD

        12/1, Delhi Mathura Road, Faridabad-121003, Haryana, India
        Tel                       :   91-129-8588895707
        E-mail                    :   nitin@mkautoindia.com
        ebsite                    :   www.mkautoindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Vijay Kumar Bhandari
                                     Mr. Nitin Bhandari; Mr.Gaurav Bhandari
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Yogesh Kalra
                                     Astt. General Manager - Exports
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components,
        Countries of Export       :   Bangladesh,Colombia,Ecuador, Guatemala, Nepal, Sri
                                     Lanka,UAE
        Quality Certification     :   TS
        About the Company:  As a leading name for friction material in the country, the MK group has
        grown exponentially over six decades since its inception in 1959, to emerge as India\'s largest supplier
        of high quality two and three-wheeler components to almost every Indian OEM as well as to the
        Indian aftermarket. As the most widely experienced automotive Clutch & Brake manufacturing
        company in India, with six state-of-the-art manufacturing facilities  spread across  north India,
        the  MK brand  has  become  synonymous  with  Clutch  Plates,  Clutch  Facings,  Brake  Linings,
        Brake Shoes, Disc Brake Pads, Forgings, Fine Blankings and Pressure Die Casted components..

         56]]></page><page Index="59"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-114
        NIPHA EXPORTS (P) LTD.
        48, Ganga Jamuna, 28/1, Shakespeare Sarani, Kolkata-700017,West Bengal, India
        Tel                       :   91-33-40214300
        Fax                       :   91-33-22875104
        E-mail                    :   nipha@niphaindia.com
        Website                   :   www.niphaindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr.Mahesh Chandra Shah
                                     Mr. Pawan Kr Shah
                                     Mr. Rakesh Shah; Mr. Anupam Shah
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Rakesh Shah, Director
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment,
        Countries of Export       :   Germany, USA, UK , Spain, Australia, Thailand and many
                                     other countries.
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015; 14001:2015; RDSO  Class-A.
        About the Company: Nipha Exports Pvt Ltd. 50 years old company. ISO Certified 9001:2015;
        14001:2015; RDSO Class-A.  We believe in motto 'Quality Comes First'. Several manufacturing
        facilities that cater to Agricultural Machinery Manufactures, Railway Industry, Power Industry and
        many more. Manufactures over 10,000 mt o f Wear Parts Annually. Export To Germany, USA,
        UK , Spain, Australia, Thailand and many other countries. Family Owned Business with 1000
        Employees, 200 Engineers and a Dedicated Design Team.

                                                              Stand No. I-115
        NIPHA INDIA (P) LIMITED

        48, Ganga Jamuna, 28/1, Shakespeare Sarani
        Kolkata-700017, West Bengal, India
        Tel                       :   91-33-40214300
        E-mail                    :   nipha@niphaindia.com
        Website                   :   www.niphaindia.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Dr. R C Shah
                                     Mr. Anupam Shah; Mr. Aakash Shah
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Aakash Shah, Associate Director
                                     Mr. Shiv Charan Choubey,Executive Assistant
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment,
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About the Company: Nipha India Pvt. Ltd was established in 1989. The Company has been
        recognized by the Government of India as a Manufacturer cum Merchant Export House. Nipha has
        its own manufacturing unit and trading division with a very good infrastructure network all over India
        and other coutries to source the finest quality of products for the benfits of the clients. Nipha has joined
        hands with manufacturers of repute for various products. Currently NIPHA has exported products
        like Transformers, ABS Plastics, Cables, Steel Rods and Bars, Pumps, Bearings, Agri-commodities,
        Irrigation equipment. Nipha adheres to strict quality control procedures for range of products.

                                                                           57]]></page><page Index="60"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-118
        MUEZ-HEST INDIA PVT. LTD

        231, Blue Rose Indl. Estate Nr. Cable Corporation
        Western Express Highway, Mumbai 400066,Maharastra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22- 240050543
        E-mail                    :   rajivaroras.ra@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.muezhest.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Syed Mohammad Javed
                                     Husain
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Tanmay Sarkar
                                     Manager-Finance
        Range of Products         :   Food Processing Machinery
        About  the Company:   Muez-Hest  offers most comprehensive technology portfolio in
        the Edible Oil Refinery, Solvent Extraction & Oleochemicals Sectors, which provides  the
        flexibility & choice to select the best technology suited for the required application.








                                                               Stand No.I-133
        NAVEENA ZEAL TECHNOLOGIES
        Near Kizhakkambalam Market, Kizhakkambalam Po,
        Ernakulam-683562,Kerala, India


        Tel                       :   91-484-2682023
        E-mail                    :   nzealtechnologies@gmail.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. George Joseph
                                     Proprietor
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. George Joseph, Proprietor
                                     Mr. Snehadas T George, Marketing Manager
        Range of Products         :   Packaging Machinery
        About the Company:  Over 20 years in the Manufacturing & trading of Packaging machines
        in Pan India. An ISO 9001: 2015 & ISO 45001:2018 certified Company. Machines ranging from
        Manual to fully automated packaging machines. Selected as the Best Inspiring Packaging Machinery
        Brand Award in 2021. Our Product range includes Hand Operated Plastic Bag sealing machines,
        Pedal operated Plastic bag sealing machines, Aluminium foil sealers, Semi automatic continuous
        band sealing machines, Cap sealers, Induction sealers, Filling machines, Labeling Machines, Vacuum
        sealers, fully automated filling and sealing machines etc.


         58]]></page><page Index="61"><![CDATA[59]]></page><page Index="62"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-136
        MW WIRETEC PVT. LTD.

        6-C, Bigjos Tower A-8,Netaji Subhash Place
        New-Delhi-110034,Delhi, India

        Tel                       :   91-11-45407714/ 800319
        E-mail                    :   works@wiretec.in
        Website                   :   www.mwwiretec.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Ajay Kapur
                                     Mr. Dev Rishi Kapur
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Akhilesh Mathur, Plant Head
                                     Mr. Ajay Kapur, Director
        Range of Products         :   Welding Tools & Equipment
        About the Company: We are Manufacturing Welding Wire, Tig Wire, Saw Waire Ss Wire and
        Flux







































         60]]></page><page Index="63"><![CDATA[Stand No.I-144
        OZLA PLASTOCRAFT PVT. LTD.
        B-26, Hosiery Complex, Phase II,
        Noida -201305 ,Uttar Pradesh, India
        Tel                       :   91-120-4165368
        E-mail                    :   ozla.plast@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.ozla.net
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Manjeet Singh
                                     Ms. Kulvinder Kaur; Mr. Prabhjeet Singh
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Prabhjeet Singh,Director
        Range of Products         :   Building Material
        Countries of Export       :   United Kingdom
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About  the Company  : Ozla Plastocraft Pvt. Ltd. Established in year 1995 is an engineering
        company based in Noida is operating under technical  collaboration with Jasun International
        Limited, England. The facility is ISO 9001-2015 and ISO 14001-2015 certified having over 36000
        square feet work space. We are  Also equipped with CAD, CAM, CNC, Tool development and cnc
        molding facilities under stringent quality control. Our products are 1) Puf Insulated overlap, Flush
        and sliding doors for cold storages, clean room etc. 2) Hinges & Locks for cold storages, swing &
        sliding Doors.  3) Modular PUF Panel for cold storages, clean room etc.
                                                              Stand No. I-126
        PETRO VALVES PVT LTD

        Survey No .1144,Opp.gharda Ghar,, Indore Highway,
        Kuha, Ahemdabad- 382433,Gujarat, India

        Tel                       :   91-79-22900001
        E-mail                    :   info@petrovalves.co.in
        Website                   :   www.petrovalves.co.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Patel Parmanand Dwarkadas
        & Participant                Managing  Director
        Range of Products         :   Pumps & Valves
        Countries of Export       :   Greece,Nigeria
        Quality Certification     :  API 6D,ISO9001:2015
        About  the Company:   We Petro Valves Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad manufacture Ball Valves,Gate
        Valves,Globe  Valves,Check  Valves applicable for various  industries like Gas, Chemicals,
        Pharmaceutical, Refineries, Petrochemicals, Oil & Gas etc.  “Petro Valves” is setting bench marks
        across GAS Pipeline Industry, across the nation. Petro Valves is authorized to use API Monogram
        under API license no 6D-0767. Petro Valves’s quality management system has been certified to ISO
        9001.


                                                                           61]]></page><page Index="64"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-173
        NOVA ENGINEERING

        III/489B, Chittilapilly, Trichur - 680 551, Kerala, Trichur-680551,Kerala, India
        Tel                       :   91-487--2306125/2306170com
        Fax                       :   91-487-2308890
        E-mail                    :   novaengg@rediffmail.com
        Website                   :   www.novaind.net
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Diljo David
        & Participant                Proprietor
        Range of Products         :   Construction & Earthmoving
                                     Machinery,Food Processing Machinery
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001-2008
        About the Company: NOVA ENGINEERING is an ISO 9001 -2008 certified Company based
        in Thrissur, Kerala, India. We are Manufacturers, Exporters  of Construction Machineries & flour
        and oil mill machines since 2002.  We are committed to manufacture and supply machinery as
        per the quality requirement of our customers efficiently in a professional manner on time and at
        right cost with customer satisfaction through continual improvement with our highly qualified
        engineers.  . From this short span of period we achieved plenty of valuable clients all over the world,
        especially in India, SriLanka, UAE, Zambia, Mauritius, Kenya, Ethiopia, Uganda, Angola, and almost
        all African countries.
                                                              Stand No. I-166
        OMKAR ENTERPRISE

        Plot No. 21, Maruti Industrial Area, Pardi-Padavala Road,
        Lothada, Rajkot, Gujarat, Rajkot-360024,Gujarat, India

        Tel                       :   91-281-9825466934
        E-mail                    :   omkarenterprise11@yahoo.com
        Website                   :   www.hydraulicpressomkar.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Balvant Hirpara
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Vadi Vipul Prabhudasbhai
                                     Engineer
                                     Mr. Lunagariya Yash Jaysukhbhai
                                     Purchase Manager
        Range of Products         :   Workshop Machinery
        About the Company : Mfg Sheet Metal Machinery & Workshop Machinery







         62]]></page><page Index="65"><![CDATA[63]]></page><page Index="66"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-168
        PIONEER COLD STORE AND CLADDING PVT. LTD.

        Plot. No.1, Tansidco Industrial Estate,
        Chennai- 604207,Tamil Nadu, India
        Tel                       :   91-44-9600175495
        E-mail                    :   sales4@pcclimitedindia.com
        Website                   :   www.isothermuae.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Vasudevan Srinivasan
        & Participant                Director
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel,Articles of Iron
                                     & Steel,Articles of Iron & Steel
        Countries of Export       :   Bangladesh,Nepal, South Africa,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About  the  Company :  PCC is Leading  Manufactures  of insulated Panels for Coldstore &
        Cladding offers a wide range of internal /external cladding solutions to designers. The base of
        our operations  is  located in  various  cities  in  South India  and supplies  carried  out to Projects
        throughout India  and neighboring countries.  An  ISO 9001: 2015 and  “ZED” Certified
        We use latest technology available to produce the quality industrial panels in large quantities on
        time.  PCC have the installed capacity to produce over 2,00,000 Sq. Meters of Insulated panels per
        Month. Panels are manufactured with Pentene blowing agent to achieve “zero ozone deposit” as
        Green initiatives.
                                                              Stand No. I-138
        PRIMAX EQUIPMENT PRIVATE LTD.

        Jalan Industrial Complex, Lane No. R-6, Baniara, Howraghat- 711411,West Bengal,India
        Tel                       :   91-33-40682148
        Fax                       :   91-33-2230-9544
        E-mail                    :   info.primaxgroup@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.primaxgroup.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Pradeep Kumar Chowdhury
                                     Ms. Bely Chowdhury
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Pradeep Kumar Chowdhury,Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Construction & Earthmoving Machinery
        Countries of Export       :   Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, Myanmar, Nepal,
                                     Sri Lanka
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About  the  Company:  The Name Primax has long been associated with Civil Construction
        Machinery & Road Construction Machinery Founded by Mr. P K Chowdhury 50 Years Back.
        Primax has maintained its lead through Entrepreneurship in indigenous Process Development. Thus
        ensuring not only good quality of products but also keeping costs within control. We have wide range
        of products of highest standard with touch of class and able to provide innovative solution to the ever
        changing needs of the construction industry. Our Products  - Concrete Batch Mixing Plant, Concrete
        Mixer, Passenger & Material Hoist, Asphalt Hot Mix Plant, Asphalt Batch Mix Plant etc.
         64]]></page><page Index="67"><![CDATA[Stand No.-B171a
        PLATINUM OVERSEAS

        Plot No 30, Jajru Industrial Area, Opp Sector 59,
        Ballabhgarh, Faridabad-121004,Haryana, India

        Tel                       :   91-999979 5911
        E-mail                    :   platinumoverseas.aakarsh@gmail.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Ashokk Arora
                                     Mr. Aakarsh Arora
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Aakarsh Arora
                                     Director
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components,Agricultural
                                     Machinery & Equipment
        About the Company: We are primarily engaged in manufacturing and exporting three wheeler
        spare parts in the after market division. At Platinum Overseas, extensive use of technology is adopted
        to ensure that all our goods are defect free and are upto the optimal quality standards. This not only
        results in repeatability of customers but also ensure the overall growth of the company as a whole.
        We have a market presence in over 3 continents across the globe. We have been into manufacturing
        of goods since  1978 and have been present in the export market for over a decade.


































                                                                           65]]></page><page Index="68"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-125
        PRISM SURFACE COATINGS PRIVATE LIMITED
        Plot No. 89, 3rd Cross, 4th Phase, Bommasandra Industrial Area
        Bangalore-560099,Karnataka, India
        Tel                       :   91-80-9742045427
        Fax                       :   91-8110-417900
        E-mail                    :   rajesh.kannan@prismsurface.com
        Website                   :   www.prismsurface.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Preetam Kumar
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Rajesh Kannan, Head - Projects
                                     Mr. Preetak Kumar,Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Material Handling Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Germany
        About the Company: Prism is one of the largest suppliers in the world supplying powder coating
        lines, Liquid painting lines, paint booths, Blasting systems etc. We have installed over 700+ coating
        lines around the world in over 30 countries. In 2014 we have acquired a German market leader in
        painting lines known as OMT Technologies based in Stuttgart, with this acquisition Prism supplies
        German engineering at Indian manufacturing costs. We have exported many lines  to European
        countries, Middle east countries and Africa countries including Egypt, Kenya, Sudan, Ghana, Togo
        etc.  Turkey supplier of Powder coating, Liquid painting plants, Paint booth, Blast room system.
                                                             Stand No. I-199c
        RAX HYDRAULICS PRIVATE LIMITED

        Plot No. M-18 Large Sector Gamharia, Industrial Area,
        Adityapur, Jamshedpur-832108,Jharkhand, India
        Tel                       :   91-95252 13070
        E-mail                    :   raxjsr@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Sujit Kumar Singh
                                     Ms. Pallavi Singh
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Rahul Kumar, Sr. Manager-Sales & Marketing
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel, Auto Components,Material
                                     Handling Equipment,Mining Equipment &
                                     Machinery
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company: Rax Hydraulics (P) Ltd.  is a reputed Manufacturer of Hydraulic Cylinders,
        Hydraulic Systems & Mill Duty Pneumatic Cylinders. Rax designs and manufactures hydraulic
        systems for varied application, including steel rolling mill, paper mills, cement plants, industrial
        furnaces, hydraulic presses, industrial automation, etc. Rax designs and manufacturers standard and
        custom hydraulic systems to meet client requirements


         66]]></page><page Index="69"><![CDATA[67]]></page><page Index="70"><![CDATA[Stand No. B171b
        REMI ELEKTROTECHNIK LTD
        Plot No.11, Cama Indl. Estate,, Goregaon East,
        Mumbai-400063,Maharastra, India


        Tel                       :   91-22-40589888
        Fax                       :   91-22-40589890
        E-mail                    :   saraf@remilabworld.com
        Website                   :   www.remilabworld.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Sunil Saraf
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Viswambhar Chiranjilal Saraf, Chairman
        Range of Products         :   Pharmaceutical Machinery,Welding Tools & Equipment
        About  the Company:  "Headquartered in Mumbai, REMI, today, is a global Laboratory and
        Blood Banking Instruments manufacturers, exporters and suppliers. The world class quality products
        and its talented team of professionals make it a premier player in the country, with a presence in
        50 countries across the globe.Today, REMI is the industry leader in manufacturing Laboratory /
        Magnetic Stirrers & Centrifuges, & Blood Bank Refrigerators / Freezers catering to over 50%
        of the total Indian demand. We are committed to maintain world-class quality standards, efficient
        delivery schedules, cost-effective rates and exceptional after sales service.

                                                               Stand No.B194a
         ROSS BOILERS
         33, Burhani Industrial Estate, Kondhwa, Budruk,
         Pune-411048,Maharastra, India
         Tel                      :   91-20-8308823383
         E-mail                   :   azhar@rossindia.com
         Website                  :   www.rossindia.com
         Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Suhail  Shaikh,Proprietor
         Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Suhail  Shaikh, Proprietor
                                     Mr. Azharuddin Shaikh,Sales Manager
         Range of Products        :   Bakery & Confectionery Machinery, Food Processing
                                     Machinery,Heating,  Ventilation, Air Conditioning &
                                     Refrigeration (HVAC-R),Machinery  for Dairy
                                     Processing,Pharmaceutical Machinery
         Quality Certification    :  ISO
         About the Company: ROSS is a leading brand name in the field of process heat equipment
         manufactured in India. We design & manufacture a wide variety of equipment such as hot water
         generators, steam boilers, thermal oil heaters, hot air generators, hot gas generators and many other
         related heating accessories. These heaters operate on practically all the industrial fuels available in
         the market in solid, liquid or gaseous form. ROSS has the distinction of launching well-engineered
         & researched products to cater to specific needs of our esteemed client.
         68]]></page><page Index="71"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-177
        ROYAL ARC ELECTRODE LTD
        6,NR Sheela Foam, Survey No.94, Paki 4, Zaroli, Umbergaon,
        Vapi, Valsad, Gujarat - 396105, Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-9004001010
        E-mail                    :   hardik@royalarc.in
        Website                   :   www.royalarc.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Hardik Sanghvi
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Tirth Amrania, Export Manager
        Range of Products         :   Welding Tools & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Chile, Guatemala,Kenya, Kuwait, Latvia
                                     Nigeria, Peru,Qatar,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO, CE , BV, LRA,etc
        About  the Company:  We would like to introduce ourselves as leading Manufacturers &
        Exporters of  Welding Electrodes, Flux Cored Wire, Solid Mig / Tig wires & Electro slag Strip
        Cladding,etc since  1986  . We are exporting to 45+ Countries  across  globe Our products  are
        approved by renowned inspection agencies like CE, ABS, LRS, DNV, ISO, BV & also approved by
        many oil companies in the world and India such as KNPC, KOC, Qatar Petroleum, IOCL, MRPL
        & Cochin refinery. The present capacity of  Electrodes division is 10000 tons, GMAW division is
        1800 tons, Flux Cored wire is 6000 tons per annum.































                                                                           69]]></page><page Index="72"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-167
        SENOR METALS PVT. LTD
        Plot-353, GIDC-II, Dared, Jamnagar-361004,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-288-2730251
        Fax                       :   91-288-2730254
        E-mail                    :   info@senormetals.in
        Website                   :   www.senormetals.in
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Rasikbhai C Shah
                                     Mr. Atul R Shah
                                     Mr. Hitesh P Shah
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Faizan Jamal,Marketing Executive
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components
        About  the Company  • Senor Metals Pvt. Ltd. established in 1998  to manufacture Copper
        Alloys  •Today is  a  USD  28 million  turnover  company •One stop  solution  for  all types  of
        Welding Consumables,  Arc  welding  Accessories,    Copper  Alloys  Products(Rods  |  Profiles  |
        Tubes | Ingots), EDM Wires (Japan Technology) ,Precision Components, MIG Welding Spares.
        •Produces  value-added special  alloys in  integrated plant which  adhere to international quality
        standards •Senor Products meet stringent requirements in Chemical and Mechanical Properties.
         •IATF 16949:2016 certified NABL Accreditated Laboratory (ISO 17025:2017) ISO 9001:2015
        CertifiedISI, IBR & IRS
                                                              Stand No. I-158
        SHARP ELECTRODES PVT LTD
        330/2C-1, Sitra Road, Sharp Nagar,, Kalapatti
        Coimbatore- 641048,Tamil Nadu, India
        Tel                       :   91-422-2628631,2627624
        Fax                       :   91-422-2627632
        E-mail                    :   jm@sharpelectrode.com
        Website                   :   www.sharpelectrodes.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Dr. J Mohanasundari
        & Participant                Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Building Material,Pumps & Valves
        Countries of Export       :   Angola, Bahrain, Canada, Guyana, Indonesia, Jamaica,
                                     Nepal, Saudi Arabia, Trinidad,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO, Lloyds Register, TUV Sud
        About the Company: SHARP ELECTRODES P LTD was established in the year 1984. The
        unit manufactures quality "SHARP" brand Welding Electrode, Dry Flux Powder & E.Q. Cut Wire
        Rods. The electrodes are approved by LLOYDS Register, London, UK., and TUV, South Asia and
        ISO 9001:2015 quality system from TUV, Asia, and also exported our quality products to various
        countries including UAE, Oman, Qatar, Mauritius, Australia, Bahrain, Nepal, USA, UK, Angola
        and many  countries. We also manufacture Sharp Brand Water lifting Pumps (Original & Pioneers
        in Pumps, the Trend Setter of Trendy model) thro' KAYJAY SHARP TRENDYS and export for
        more than 40 yrs
         70]]></page><page Index="73"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-139
        SHIV-OM BRASS INDUSTRIES
        Plot No. 3690/3691, Road No. 7, Near Pramukhswami Circle
        G.I.D.C. Phase 3, Dared, Jamnagar-361005,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-288-6643600
        E-mail                    :   snehal@shivombrass.in
        Website                   :   www.shivombrass.co.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Snehal Gohel
        & Participant                Director
        Range of Products         :   Brass & Steel Inserts, Cable Lugs, Split
                                     Bolts, Terminal, Connectors, Special Fasteners, etc.
        Countries of Export       :   Germany, United Kingdom
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001-2015
        About the Company : Shiv-Om Brass Industries, having headquartered at Jamnagar city located
        in India, is one of the leading Manufacturers & Exporters of Precision Turned Components, Brass
        & Steel Inserts, Cable Lugs, Split Bolts, Terminal, Connectors, Special Fasteners, and Insulator and
        Standoff Spacers, Electrical Switch Boxes etc. We manufacture parts in Brass, Aluminium, Copper,
        Stainless Steel & Mild Steel. Kindly note that we are manufacturing all parts IN – HOUSE.



                                                             Stand No. I-199E
        POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA
        B-9, Qutub Institutional Area, Katwaria Sarai
        Gurgaon-110016,Haryana, India
        Tel                       :   91-11-26560121,98735-4
        Fax                       :   91-11-26560039
        E-mail                    :   atandon@powergridindia.com
        Website                   :   www.powergrid.in
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. V. K.Singh
                                     Mr. Abhay Choudhary; Mr. R. K. Tyagi
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Anshuman Tandon, Sr General Manager
        Range of Products         :   Consulancy for Transmission Projects
        About  the Company:  Power  Grid  Corporation  of  India  Limited(POWERGRID),  is  a
        ‘Maharatna’ Public Sector Enterprise of Govt. of India. POWERGRID owns & operates 1,72,876
        ckm Transmission Lines and 267 Sub-Stations with >99 % System Availability and 4,85,777 MVA
        of Transformation  Capacity. POWERGRID  with its  brand name  ‘POWERTEL’ in Telecom
        business  is  the only Telecom Service  Provider in the Country having PAN India overhead
        Optic fiber network. Company has an all India Broad Band Telecom Network of  75,636 Km.
        POWERGRID provides Transmission related consultancy to more than 150 domestic lients and
        has Global footprints in 23 countries catering more that 25 clients.


                                                                           71]]></page><page Index="74"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-155
        SHREE SAI STEELS

        Plot No. 132-133, Huda, Sector 59, Ballabgarh
        Faridabad-121004,Haryana, India
        Tel                       :   91-129- 9810602799
        E-mail                    :   omsai.fbd@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.shreesaisteels.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Anuj Gupta
        & Participant                Director
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel
        About the Company : Shree Sai Steels, a professionally organized group, holds a strong landmark
        presence in the steel industry, since 1982. Being a pioneer in steel, we are engaged in Manufacturing
        and Supplying wide range of C/Z Purlings,Crimp Sheets And Flashing Trims, Pre Engineered
        Buildings, etc. Apart from this, we also trade and supply qualitative assortment of HR Coils, SS
        Sheets, Color Coated Coils, etc. We use pre painted galvanized steel, pre painted galvalume steel
        from premier producers to produce a superior quality and environment friendly product, a one of
        its kind in India matching with International Standard of Steel Design and Strength.





































         72]]></page><page Index="75"><![CDATA[Stand No.-I-134
        SONA CYCLE INDUSTRIES
        C-162, Phase-V,, Focal Point, Ludhiana-141010, Punjab, India
        Tel                       :   91-161-2676501
        Fax                       :   91-161-2677344
        E-mail                    :   sonacycle@hotmail.com
        Website                   :   www.sonaworld.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Suresh Gupta, Proprietor
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Mukul Gupta,CEO
        Range of Products         :   Two/Three Wheelers,
        Countries of Export       :   Bahrain, Bangladesh, Egypt,Myanmar, Sri Lanka,Uganda,
                                     Zambia
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About  the Company:  Sona   Cycle  Industries  was  established  in  the  year  of  1969. We    are
        an ISO  9001:2015 certified  company. our "SONA"  products  are adhered to stringent quality
        measures and every effort is taken to produce flawless products to meet international standards.
        With increase in exports over the yearsand higher customer satisfaction the government of
        India honoured our company with one Star Export House.  Products: all types of bicycle for
        Kids(14/16/20), MTB(20/24/26/27.5 & Atandard Roadster Models(20\""/22\"") Bicycle Parts:
        Freewheel, Chainwheel & Crank, Framehub & Parts, Brake Set & Partssaddle, Pedals Bb Axle &
        Cups, Chain Covers, Pumps, Forks, Chain, Handle Bell & other accessories.

































                                                                           73]]></page><page Index="76"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-199A
        SHRI VISHVAKARMA (EMERY STONES)

        Vishvakarma Nagar, , P.O. Saradhana , Ajmer-305206,Rajasthan, India
        Tel                       :   91-145-9829072228
        E-mail                    :   sgs@choyal.com
        Website                   :   www.choyal.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Shrigopal Sharma
                                     Mr. Rs Choyal
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Yash Vardhan Choyal,
                                     General Manager- Marketing and Administration
                                     Mr.  Shrigopal Sharma, Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment,
        Countries of Export       :   Australia, Brazil, Hong Kong, Kenya, Nepal, Oman,Saudi
                                     Arabia, Singapore, Sri Lanka, Tanzania,Uganda,UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO, CE
        About  the Company : We are the leading manufacturer of Flour Mill and Emery stones
        from India for the last 55 years. Our expertise is in Flour mill, Emery stones, Turnkey solutions,
        automation, power saving, grain processing, grain storage, and handling. We pioneer in the
        world of Flour Mills & Emery Stones by meeting the requirements of many quality-conscious
        global  markets and exporting Flour Mills & Emery Stones to more than 20 countries.
        We were the very first exporter from India in this sector (1970) and the unit was awarded “Certificate
        for Excellence in Export” year after year.
                                                              Stand No.-I-146
        SINGHSONS REFRIGERATION
        115  Hiranandani Industrial Es, Tatekanjur Marg (W), Mumbai-400078, Maharastra, India
        Tel                       :   91-22-25782450
        Fax                       :   91-22-25791775
        E-mail                    :   singhsonsrefrigeration@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.singhsonsref.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Gaganjit Singh
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Gaganjit Singh, Partner
                                     Mr. Amandeep Singh, Partner
        Range of Products         :   Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning
                                     & Refrigeration (HVAC-R),Food  Processing Machinery
        Countries of Export       :   Algeria,Chad,Malawi,Saudi Arabia, Sudan
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company : We are an innovative refrigeration and air-conditioning business group
        with a range of operations from conceptual design to commissioning. Headquartered in Mumbai,
        we have been in the business of refrigeration and air-conditioning for decades, boasting some of
        the most coveted technical qualifications and experience in servicing 100s of clients across domains
        and geographies. We aim to deliver the latest, state-of-the-art technological solutions with the
        highest added value, at a competitive cost benefiting all our customers. Our company has boldly
        transformed to build solid value for our customers by providing them with industrial refrigeration
        and air-conditioning solutions.
         74]]></page><page Index="77"><![CDATA[75]]></page><page Index="78"><![CDATA[Stand No. B101a
        SPEEDCRAFTS INFRATECH  PRIVATE
        Layak Bhawan, Boring Canal Road, Patna-800001,Bihar, India
        Tel                      :   91-612-2534514
        Fax                      :   91-612-2534914
        E-mail                   :   patna@speedcrafts.com
        Website                  :   www.speedcrafts.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Satyendra Kumar Agarwala
                                    Mr. Shashank Agarwala
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Shashank Agarwala, Director
                                    Mr. Kushagra Agarwal, Manager Exports
        Range of Products        :   Construction & Earthmoving Machinery
        Countries of Export      :   Algeria, Bangladesh, Cambodia, Cameroon, Congo,
                                    Democratic Republic of the, Kenya, Madagascar,
                                    Nepal, Nigeria,Uganda
        Quality Certification    :  ISO 9001:2015
        About  the Company :  Speedcrafts  is  a  leading Indian  Engineering  Industry engaged in
        manufacture of Road & Highway Construction Equipment with supplies to over 60 Countries
        around the World.  Our product range includes Asphalt Drum Mix Plant, Asphalt Batching Plant,
        Mobile Asphalt Plant, Concrete Batching Plant, Bitumen Decanter, Bitumen Distributor, Road
        Sweeper, Chip Spreader, Pothole Repairing Machine, Asphalt Paver, Diesel Road Roller  Road
        Marking Machine & Preheater, Aggregate Crusher, etc.
                                                              Stand No. I-150
        SRI BHAVANI CASTINGS LTD
        2-144 & 145, Santhi Nagar,Kakinada- 533005
        Andhra Pradesh, India
        Tel                       :   91-884-2372211/12/13
        Fax                       :   91-884-2347803
        E-mail                    :   info@sbcl.in
        Website                   :   www.sbcl.in
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Karipineni Sashikanth
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Karipineni Sashikanth, Executive Director
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components, Agricultural  Machinery &
                                     Equipment,Electrical  Machinery & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Sri Lanka
        Quality Certification     :   TS
        About the Company: Sri Bhavani Castings Ltd is 46 yrs Precious S.G and Cast Iron Components
        Manufacturing Foundry located in Kakinada, Andhra Pradesh State. India with  I.E HPML (6050
        KOYO), 300 & 450 Arfa Lines, Eirich Sand Plant (40mt/hr), 33 kv  line having in house fully
        equipped MSD with VMC,CNC,SPMS & GPMS etc., and QAD/LAB with CMM, Tessa Height
        Gauge, Profile Projector and Chemical Lab etc., with Quality Certification of IATF 16949/iso9001
        and product range of Brake Drums, Brackets, Shackles, Clutch, Earth Moving Parts, Gear Shifter
        Forks, Harvester Parts, Aqua and Insulators etc to customers defence, BEML, ASRTU, OEMS,
        exports and after market.
         76]]></page><page Index="79"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-176
        SRP CRANE CONTROLS (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED

        Plot No 39, Jaydev Ind. Estate, Sr No 202, Opp. Inova Cast,
        Essen Road, NH 27, Shapar, Rajkot-360024,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-8000788873
        E-mail                    :   info@srpcranecontrols.com
        Website                   :   www.srpcranecontrols.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Ashvinbhai Jethabhai Khanpara
                                     Mr. Kushalkumar Pradhyumanbhai
                                     Khanpara
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Pritkumar Pradhyumanbhai
                                     Khanpara, Technical Head
                                     Mr. Ashvinbhai Jethabhai Khanpara
                                     Director
        Range of Products         :   Material Handling Equipment
        About the Company : We are manufacturing best in class Industrial Crane Wireless Remote
        Control and customized Remotes too , it is being used in all type of industries like Automotive,
        Mining ,General Manufacturing and Shipyards too , We have mission to design and deliver best
        in  class  material  handling solutions. We  are  manufacturer  of all type of EOT  Crane  Control
        Equipment.

































                                                                           77]]></page><page Index="80"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-142
        STRIKING INTERNATIONAL

        SCO 1 and 2 Above OBC/PNB Bank, G T Road,
        Sahnewal, Ludhiana-141120,Punjab, India
        Tel                       :   91-161-2847321
        Fax                       :   91-161-2847321
        E-mail                    :   striking.intl@hotmail.com
        Website                   :   www.strikinginternational.com
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Gurender Dhand, Director
                                     Mr. Gagandeep Singh, Export Manager
        Countries of Export       :   Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bolivia, Cambodia, Djibouti,
                                     Dominican Republic, Egypt, Ethiopia,Kenya,Peru,
                                     Qatar,Syria
        About  the Company:  We are pleased to introduce  ourselves  as  STRIKING
        INTERNATIONAL  as one of the leading manufacturers & exporters from India of Tyres,
        Tubes  &  Friction  Brake  (BRAKELININGs)  are  already exporting  to  around  57 countries
        Including, Most of Middle East countries, Africa & Latin American countries.1. Agricultural Tyres
        Nylon Range  Made  in  India.  (ALLIGATOR  Brand)  2.  Forklift  &  OTR  Sizes  Nylon Range
        Made  in  India.  (ALLIGATOR  Brand)  3.  Solid Tyres  Made  in  India.  (ALLIGATOR  Brand)
        4. Automotive Tyres All Bias from India. (ALLIGATOR Brand) 5. Butyl Tubes Made in India
        (ALLIGATOR Brand) The STRIKING group is focused on three parameters .
                                                               Stand No.I-128
        HEAT BIRD PVT LTD
        340-B-7, GIDC Industrial Est., Makarpura, Vadodara-390010,Gujarat, India

        Tel                       :   91-9925028439
        E-mail                    :   heatbird12@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.heatbird.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Ravi Bhavsar,
        & Participant                CEO
        Range of Products         :   Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning
                                     & Refrigeration (HVAC-R),Wire & Cables
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2008 & CE
        About the Company :
        Since its inception in 1986, the Manufacturing and Exporting company Ambica Enterprises, has
        developed into a trustful entity and pioneered the industry by providing high performing Industrial
        Heaters and Thermocouples. Owing to our diversified technical and professional expertise, we have
        developed a wide range of revolutionary products that earned us the most reputable ISO 9001:2008
        & CE certification. We strive to deliver products with peak performance that are innovative, custom
        designed, easy to install and operate, require low maintenance, and serve a durable service life.

         78]]></page><page Index="81"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-178
        SUMITEK NATRAJ MACHINERY PRIVATE LIMITED
        564, Kathwada GIDC, Opp. Road No. 10
        Near Tribhuvan Estate Gate Kathwada
        Ahemdabad-382430,Gujarat, India

        Tel                       :   91-79-9376105240
        E-mail                    :   md@sumiteknatraj.com
        Website                   :   www.sumiteknatraj.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Dinesh Mistry
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Dinesh Mistry
                                     Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Plastic Machinery
        About the Company: Manufacturer & Exporter of Plastic Injection Molding Machine








                                                              Stand No. I-120
        TECHNOCRATS PLASMA SYSTEMS PRIVATE LIMITED
        Unit Nos 6,7& 8. Nirav-2, Gaon Devi Industrial Complex.
        Sativali Vasai East, Mumbai-401208, Maharastra, India
         Tel                      :   91-93228793960
        E-mail                    :   md@technocratplasma.com
        Website                   :   www.technocratplasma.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Arun Kumar
                                     Ms. Vandana Sharma
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Arun Kumar, Managing Director
        Range of Products         :   Welding Tools & Equipment
        Countries of Export       :   Chile,Kuwait,Nigeria, Saudi Arabia,Uganda
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company: Manufacturer of Technologically advanced Plasma Cutting Machines
        for Cutting Thicknesses up to 100 mm. welding machines for MMAW/TIG Welding, Mig/Mag
        Welding, Saw Welding, AC/DC Tig, Plasma Welding, CNC 6-Axis Plate /Pipe Profile Cutting
        Machines, H-Beam Production Line, Cnc Drilling Machines , Welding Process Automation for all
        types of Welding Applications, Wear Plates Manufacturing Plant.


                                                                           79]]></page><page Index="82"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-172
        TEJAS POLYMERS AND ENGINEERS

        W-43, MIDC, Bhosari, Pune- 411026,Maharastra, India

        Tel                       :   91-20-27122680
        E-mail                    :   tejask86@hotmail.com
        Website                   :   www.tejastraileraxle.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Arvind Bhikaji Kale
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Tejas Arvind Kale, GM
        Range of Products         :   Agricultural Machinery & Equipment
        Quality Certification     :  ISO9001:2015
        About the Company : Tejas Polymers And Engineers was started in the year 1989. Its Proprietor,
        Mr Arvind B Kale is a graduate in Automobile Engineering and Specialization done in Agriculture
        Engineering from England. The company is into design and fabrication of agriculture trailer of
        various capacities as per the requirement of the end customer and into supply of its spare parts like
        trailer axles, tow eye, hinges, hydraulic cylinders and other parts required for agriculture trailer. Tejas
        Polymers And Engineers started its exports with Tanzania and now are exporting to Zambia also.
        We are into design of DAIRY FARM related products like water-trough,TMR,Saw-dust-spreader.


































         80]]></page><page Index="83"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-152
        TFI FILTRATION (INDIA) PRIVATE LIMITED

        Shed No.88 To 91, Gantotri Ind, Us.,Estate, Nr. Ramol Cross Ro, Ad,
        Phase-4, G.I.D.C., Vatva, Ahemdabad-382445, Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-79-48998003
        E-mail                    :   account@tfipl.com
        Website                   :   www.tfipl.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Anandkumar Arvindkumar Bhatt
                                     Ms. Sarojben Arvindkumar Bhatt
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Vinay Kanubhai Makwana
                                     Asst. Manager - Sales
                                     Mr. Anandkumar Arvindkumar Bhatt
                                     Director - Technical & Operations
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel
        Countries of Export       :   Egypt,Indonesia,Saudi Arabia,UAE,UK,USA
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015
        About the Company: Our Company Manufactures and Supplied all Kind of Industrial Filters
        and Filtration Producst . We are Specialized in Cleanable and Reusable Type Filters and Filtration
        Producsts.


                                                              Stand No. I-121
        TOSY AUTO PRODUCTS

        A-34/28, Guru Nanak Pura, Vikas Marg
        Delhi-110092, India
        Tel                       :   91-11-9811435115
        E-mail                    :   mail@tosyauto.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr.Vishal Bhalla
        & Participant                Partner
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components,Agricultural Machinery &
                                     Equipment,Construction & Earthmoving
                                     Machinery,Wire & Cables
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001-2015
        About the Company: Manufacturer of:- 1 Assy. Oil & Fuel Flexible Hoses And Pipes
        2 Assy. Hydraulic And Air Brake Hoses 3 Assy. Fuel Injection Pipes 4 Assy. Oil & Lubricating
        Brake  Tubes 5 Assy. Power Steering Hoses 6 Hydraulic And Lift Hoses
        7 Egr Pipes  8 Epdm Hoses  9 Speedometer and Control Cables 10 Propeller Shafts and
        Components





                                                                           81]]></page><page Index="84"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-117
        TRIKON MACHINE PVT. LTD.

        UG-2, Siddhartha Chambers,55-A, Kalu Sarai, Hauz Khas
        New-Delhi-110016,Delhi, India
        Tel                       :   91-11-26564030
        Fax                       :   91-11-26561792
        E-mail                    :   vipulgupta@vsapl.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Vipul Gupta
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Vipul Gupta, Director
                                     Mr. Rahul Agarwal,Head - Export Market
        Range of Products         :   Construction & Earthmoving Machinery,Mining
                                     Equipment & Machinery
        Quality Certification     :  ISO
        About the Company: The Company deals is Quality Spare Parts for Aggregate Processing Plants
        like Stone Crushers, Batching Plants, Asphalt Plants, Concrete Pumps, Shotcrete Machines etc.
        Replacement Parts are made for major popular brands of the world like Metso, Sandvik, Schwing,
        Putzmeister, CIFA etc.



                                                               Stand No.I-156
        UNIQUE ENGINEERING ENTERPRISES PRIVATE LIMITED
        Shed No.42,Phase II,Ida Cherlapally
        Hyderabad-500051,Telangana, India


        Tel                       :   91-40-9553321747
        E-mail                    :   sales@unique1972.com
        Website                   :   www.unique1972.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Moiz Mansoor Najmi
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Azim Jiwani
                                     Business Development Manager
        Range of Products         :   Articles of Iron & Steel,Construction &
                                     Earthmoving Machinery,Pumps &
                                     Valves
        About the Company
        We are a one stop solution providers for products used in Oil exploration,Cement,Steel,Sugar,Mi
        ning and Construction industries.





         82]]></page><page Index="85"><![CDATA[83]]></page><page Index="86"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-147
        UNIQUE WELDING PRODUCTS PVT LTD

        701/B, GIDC Estate,Phase -IV, Anand-388121,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-2692-236092
        E-mail                    :   rohit@uniquewelding.com
        Website                   :   www.uniquewelding.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Rohit Mulchandani
                                     Mr. Kamal Mulchandani
                                     Mr. Amar Sugnomal Mulchandani
        Name of the Participants   :   Mr. Rohit Mulchandani, Director
                                     Mr. Kamal Mulchandani, Director
        Range of Products         :   Wire & Cables,Food Processing Machinery
        Countries of Export       :   Brazil,Mexico,United Arab Emirates,Vietnam
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 9001:2015 , CE APPROVAL
        About the Company: We are one of the leading manufacturers of MIG/Co2 Welding Wires and
        Sub-merged Arc Welding Wires & TIG Welding Wires in INDIA- since 1987.2.We are suppliers
        to well known Automobile, Engineering and Pipe Manufacturers in INDIA. We produce Welding
        Wires in following Grades: As per AWS - ER70S6,ER70S2, EL8, EL12, EM12K, EA2, ER80G,
        ER90G etc.  We are ISO 9001:2015 certified and also hold CE Marking for export to europe.
        Presently we export to UAE, VIETNAM, MEXICO,BRAZIL. For more details please visit www.
        uniquewelding.com
                                                              Stand No. I-174
        UNITECHENGINEERING
        C-3 DSIDC Complex Rohtak Road Nangloi
        Delhi-110041, India

        Tel                       :   91-11-9818560171
        E-mail                    :   unitech.engineering58@gmail.com
        Website                   :   www.unitracparts.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Nitin Saxena
        & Participant                Manager
        Range of Products         :   Hand Tools & Power Tools
        About the Company: The Company has grown into a global exporter and become one of the
        largest supplier and exporter for Automobile Components aftermarket parts in the world which
        includes in the field of Two-Wheelers parts, Three Wheelers parts, Cars parts, Tractors, Earth moving
        Machines components and as well as trailers parts. These aftermarket components are distributing
        to a growing customer base in over 10 countries.






         84]]></page><page Index="87"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-132
        USHA LINER SHAPAR PVT LTD

        Survey No. 266, Plot No.10-11, Shapar, Dist Rajkot
        Rajkot-360024,Gujarat, India
        Tel                       :   91-9537990888
        E-mail                    :   info@ushaliner.com
        Website                   :   www.ushaliner.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Hansrajbhai V Lunagariya
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Sagar H Lunagariya, Business Development Head
                                     Mr. Malay H Lunagariya,
                                     Business Development Executive
        Range of Products         :   Auto Components,Articles of Iron & Steel
        About the Company : Accuracy, Quality & Supply of our finished product with punctuality,
        state us with good reputation in domestic and overseas market since last 46 years.
        We’re leading producer of Best Quality Cylinder Liners & Sleeves for All Engines as following.
        Cylinder Liners & Sleeves For: Automobiles And Car Engines, Compressor and Refrigeration
        Engines, Heavy Duty Engines (Bus and Trucks), Earth Moving Equipment Engines
        Generators, Tractor Engines, Water Outboard Engines, Agricultural Oil Engines
        Marine Engines
        Quality Policy : “To supply with quality & surety is the genuine view of connoisseur.”
        We earnestly would like to make pronounced business with your esteem company.
                                                               Stand No.I-131
        WESMAN THERMAL ENGINEERING PRO
        Wesman Center, 8, Mayfair Road
        Kolkata-700019,West Bengal, India

        Tel                       :   91-33-4002 0300/0301
        Fax                       :   91-33-2281-6402
        E-mail                    :   combustion@wesman.com
        Website                   :   www.wesman.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Nikhil Vaswani
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Arnab Ganguly, Senior Manager
        Range of Products         :   Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning
                                     & Refrigeration (HVAC-R)
        About the Company: Wesman Thermal is India’s leading supplier of combustion systems. Our
        burners are the first choice of OEMs, consultants and users in sectors from metals, food processing
        and chemicals to ceramics, forgings and cement. Our combustion range covers: * Oil, gas and dual-
        fuel burners  *Regenerative burners  *Self-recuperative burners*Fans and blowers*Oil filtering,
        heating and pumping systems *Ratio and pressure regulating valves * Ignition and flame failure
        systems  *Burner  management panels. Wesman  also  designs  custom  combustion  solutions,  from
        basic manual functions to automated process control.

                                                                           85]]></page><page Index="88"><![CDATA[Stand No.B101
        VENTILATION ENGINEERING CO PVT LTD.
        12th Floor, Suite-11, Chatterjee Int.Centre,
        33A JLN Road, Kolkata-700071,West Bengal, India
        Tel                      :   91-33-9831179093
        Fax                      :   91-33-22263882
        E-mail                   :   ventduct@gmail.com
        Website                  :   www.ductsandhoses.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Tejash Shah
                                    Mr. Bulbul Shah; Ms. Siddhi T Shah
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Tejash Bulbul Shah,Director
        Range of Products        :   Heating, Ventilation, Air Conditioning & Refrigeration
                                    (HVAC-R),Mining Equipment & Machinery
        Countries of Export      :   Australia,Bhutan,Germany,Nepal, Saudi Arabia,UAE
        About the Company : Manufacturers and Exporters of PVC Ventilation Ductings from 200mm
        to 3500mm dia. & Industrial Fans to be used  in  Mines,  Tunnels & Road Ventilation. PVC
        SEMIRIGID Ventilation Ductings in 10M lengths  to be used for Exhaust & Blower Application
        and PVC Blower Ductings  in  25/50/100mtr. lengths used  for only Blower Application  and
        Elliptical Twin Ducts where space constraint is there in 25/50M lengths. We also manufacture FR
        and AS Ducts as per IS:3768/1996 to be used in Underground Coal Mines. We also manufacture
        various types of small diameter Hoses from 32mm to 600mm dia. For Further details vist  website
        www.ductsandhoses.com
































         86]]></page><page Index="89"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-119
        VGK ELECTRIC VEHICLE INDUSTRY PVT LTD

        A-907 J.P Apartment Flat No. B-5 Shalimar Garden Extn-1
        Dadri-201005, Ghaziabad,   Uttar Pradesh,India

        Tel                       :   91-98116 64886
        E-mail                    :   gurinder@vgkev.com
        Name of the Chief Executive   :   Mr. Gurinder Singh Oberoi
        & Participant                Director
        Range of Products         :   Battery Operated Bikes and E
                                     Rickshaw
        About the Company : Manufacturer of Battery Operated Bikes and E Rickshaw












































                                                                           87]]></page><page Index="90"><![CDATA[Stand No. I-157
        YAMA ENGINEERS & TESTING INSTRUMENTS PVT LTD
        16/6, Y.P. Powar Nagar, Kolhapur-416012, Maharastra, India
        Tel                       :   91-231-2690766
        Fax                       :   91-231 2640494
        E-mail                    :   yamaengineers@yahoo.co.in
        Website                   :   www.yamaengineers.com
        Name of the Chief Executives   :   Mr. Suresh Dattatray Mandlik
                                     Mr. Vishal Suresh Mandlik
                                     Mr.Shubhada Suresh Mandlik
        Name of the Participant   :   Mr. Vishal Suresh Mandlik, Director
        Range of Products         :   Hand Tools & Power Tools
        Countries of Export       :   UAE
        Quality Certification     :  ISO 17025
        About  the Company:  Established in  1984, Yama Engineers & Testing  Instruments  Pvt. Ltd.
        has  cemented its  place as  a significant entity in  manufacture and export of various  range of
        testing machines. The success of the enterprise can be thoroughly  ascribed to the quality and
        reasonable prices of its products. The range of products:   Universal Testing Machines (Electronic
        / Mechanical)   Impact Testing Machines (YIT) as per ASTM / ISO / BS EN / IS standards
         Motorized notching machine   Plastic Impact Testing Machines as per ASTM / ISO DIN standards
        Hardness Testers (Electronic / Mechanical)   Electronic Measuring Systems
































         88]]></page><page Index="91"><![CDATA[89]]></page><page Index="92"><![CDATA[Basic Swahili for Travellers























































         90]]></page><page Index="93"><![CDATA[91]]></page><page Index="94"><![CDATA[92]]></page><page Index="95"><![CDATA[93]]></page><page Index="96"><![CDATA[94]]></page><page Index="97"><![CDATA[95]]></page><page Index="98"><![CDATA[Important Contact Numbers


                 Indian Diplomatic Mission in Tanzania


                 High Commission of India in Tanzania
                 Shaaban Robert Street, Plot No. 213/51, P.O. Box 2684, Dar es Salaam.
                 Tel:+255-22-2113094/2113096
                 Fax:+255-22-6373451
                 https://hcindiatz.gov.in
                 Key Contact person
                 Shri. Raj K Ganger
                 Second Secretary (Com.,P&I) & Commercial Representative
                 High Commission of India
                 Dar-es-Salaam, Tanzania
                 comm.desalaam@mea.gov.in




                 Hospitals
                 Aga Khan Hospital
                 Ocean Road Dar es Salaam TZ, Tanzania
                 +255 22 211 5151
                 www.agakhanhospitals.org/DarEsSalaam
                 Muhimbili National Hospital
                 Malik Rd, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 +255 22 215 1367
                 www.mnh.or.tz
                 CCBRT Hospital
                 Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 +255 699 990 002
                 www.ccbrt.or.tz






         96]]></page><page Index="99"><![CDATA[Fire Station
                 Address:Morogoro Rd, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Phone :+255 652 356 406


                 Police Station
                 Kibada Police Station
                 Address: 485Q+PG7, Tungi Road, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania


                 Banks
                 Diamond Trust Bank
                 Address: 57JM+4MF, Jamaat Street, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Phone: +255 22 211 4891
                 I&M Bank (T) LTD
                 Address: Livingstone St, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Phone: +255 22 218 1072
                 CRDB Bank
                 Address: 57RJ+F4W, Olympio St, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania


                 Shopping Centers
                 Mlimani City Mall
                 Sam Nujoma Road, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Daily, from 8:00 AM till 11:00 PM
                 info@mlimanicity.co.tz
                 022 241 1644
                 Quality Center Mall
                 Pugu Road 255 Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Aura Mall
                 Morogoro Road Dar es Salaam, Tanzania










                                                                           97]]></page><page Index="100"><![CDATA[Car Rental Services
                 Xpress Rent A Car
                 Address: 982 Senegal Street, Upanda, Dar es Salaam 5572, Tanzania
                 Areas served:
                 Tanzania
                 Phone: +255 22 215 2394
                 Budget Car Rentals
                 Address: Zanaki St, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Hours:  Open 24 hours
                 Phone: +255 716 786 123
                 Smiles Rent A Car Services Limited
                 Address: Rita tower, Simu St, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania
                 Phone: +255 783 447 239

        Key  Tourist attractions in  Tanzania

                 1.    Mount Kilimanjaro
                 2.    Serengeti National Park
                 3.    Zanzibar Beaches
                 4.    Ngorongoro Conservation Area
                 5.    Lake Manyara National Park
                 6.    Mafia Island
                 7.    Tarangire National Park
                 8.    Pemba Island
                 9.    Stone Town
                 10.   Selous Game Reserve
                 11.   Arusha National Park
                 12.   Ruaha National Park
                 13.   Gombe Stream National Park
                 14.   Katavi National Park
                 15.   Lake Victoria



         98]]></page><page Index="101"><![CDATA[99]]></page><page Index="102"><![CDATA[EEPC INDIA OFFICES
        Registered & Head Office            H.O. (Cell)
        Vanijya Bhavan (1st Floor)          Vandhna (4th Floor),11 Tolstoy Marg
        International Trade Facilitation Centre   New Delhi-110 001
        1/1 Wood Street, Kolkata-700 016    Tel : 91-11-23353353, 23711124/25
        Tel : 91-33-22890651/52/53          E-mail : eepcto@eepcindia.net
        E-mail : eepcho@eepcindia.net

                                 REGIONAL OFFICES
        Chennai                             Kolkata
        EEPC INDIA                          EEPC INDIA
        Greams Dugar (3rd Floor)            Vanijya Bhavan (2nd Floor)
        149 Greams Road, Chennai-600 006    International Trade Facilitation Centre
        Tel : 91-44-28295501/5502           1/1 Wood Street, Kolkata-700 016
        E-mail : eepcrochen@eepcindia.net   Tel : 91-33-22890673/74
                                            E-mail : eepcrokol@eepcindia.net
        Mumbai                              New Delhi
        EEPC INDIA                          EEPC INDIA
        B-202 & 220, Aurus Chambers         Flat No.10, P, Q, N, 10th Floor
        Annex "B", 2nd Floor, Behind Mahindra Tower   DCM Building, 16 Barakhamba Road
        S. S. Amrutwar Marg, Worli ,Mumbai-400 013   New Delhi - 110 001
        Tel : 91-22-42125555                Tel : 91-11-23314171/74
        E-mail : eepcromum@eepcindia.net    E-mail : eepcrodel@eepcindia.net

                               SUB-REGIONAL OFFICES
        Ahmedabad                           Bangalore
        EEPC INDIA                          EEPC INDIA
        TF- 313/A (3rd Floor), ATMA House   Embassy Square, 103, First Floor
        Ashram Road, Ahmedabad-380 009      No.148, Infantry Road, Bengaluru - 560001
        Tel : 91-79-26588720                                 Tel : 91-80-22261396 / 22268669
        E-mail : eepcsroahd@eepcindia.net   E-mail : eepcsroblr@eepcindia.net

        Hyderabad                           Jalandhar
        EEPC INDIA                          EEPC INDIA
        Soham Mansion (1st Floor)           Plot Comm. 1, Focal Point
        No. 5-4-187/3 & 4/4, M.G. Road      Jalandhar-144 012
        Secunderabad-500 003                Tel : 91-181-2602264
        Tel : 91-40-27536704                E-mail : eepcsrojld@eepcindia.net
        E-mail : eepcsrohyd@eepcindia.net

                              Website : www.eepcindia.org
                             CIN : U51900WB1955NPL022644

         100]]></page><page Index="103"/><page Index="104"/><page Index="105"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="106"><![CDATA[]]></page></pages></Search>
